<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="03f72f70-7a00-4dbb-93b7-6c7f65954fc5" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA["If you fight for a cause then fight for a cause!" http://youtu.be/fFb3u6kzdAY #riots #truth		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wow. This is a really REALLY cool Wheatley. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YzG94ct2d5k		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Do you still model props/build levels for your current games or is it purely designing and delegating?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: 'DRM scheme that ENCOURAGES piracy is insane.'		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username No, dear god, no. You should buy something like this instead. It's even red&black! http://t.co/Z1k7OsH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is cute and stuff. http://t.co/vnhHczd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Seems my Lowpoly Contest is quite a success. I wonder how many more people enter during this weekend... http://t.co/t1tkL6X		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username http://t.co/tNCOEzeZ More like Designer From Hell... Semi-bold is a perfectly valid request: http://t.co/EKQ8pd7V		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It looks like... LG has finally pushed an upgrade for my phone!?¡¿ No more Android Cupcake 1.5!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Yesssss. Yes yes yes. It's now running froyo 2.2.2.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If I ever turn out to be absurdely rich, I'm going to buy a Clenet. http://t.co/eb5CLrko		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No offense, but [insert offensive words here]		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username: any specific reason there's so much whitespace? You can easily have the wings twice as big as they are now, if you optimize the UV.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So... I just realized that the 2 series I like most are House, and Castle. Fun coinkidink.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: "Our TF2 art thread has nearly 4 THOUSAND more replies than the WAYWO threa." But it's also over twice as old... ;)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This short movie is brilliant! Everyone who does 3D art will love it: http://t.co/LHPpClKD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This makes me feel so sad: RT @username: @username: The future of games at retail http://t.co/rfSKaLsd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username That's because Eskimo's don't have all that many words for snow. The Sami, however, do.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So this 3D marketing trend has really gone too far now. Why? 3D toothpaste...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: I spent a week in Boston while my son was having a medical procedure done."   Is he a Strogg now?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Well, this got a crapload of responses... http://t.co/MhDfGOrd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: "A guide on how to get more free space with Dropbox! http://t.co/4UHiMwUH Retweet for a chance to get +100GB!" Mmmm. Spaaace.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Screw you, Garshasp. After wrestling with clunky controls for 4 hours, your last savegame is 3 hours ago? *Installs Prince of Persia*		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Yup. We're living in the future. Invisibility http://t.co/F9FCLGw9 holograms http://t.co/3AIUfSoN and 'free' energy http://t.co/Cb9sAqkR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Worst news I heard about my country in a looong time: http://t.co/N3EmwKF1 Stupid copyright hypocrits.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username The DLC is sold as 'steampunk' and not as 'christmas' pack, so I see no reason for it to be temporary. Not 100% certain, though.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username - took a couple of minutes to whip this up: http://t.co/2UMqOKcH PSD: http://t.co/NMiSDWSE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Are you sure you want to know that? http://t.co/LnkaYKAR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just saw a well-dressed man casually whacking the bejeezus out of a boxing bag with an umbrella. I'm done for today. http://t.co/BawwTgQ7		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Steam just broke the 5 million user barrier! http://t.co/L3Li3wmH statistics&data: http://t.co/bWtmw55W		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Made a background today. Warning: it's a bit bright.  http://t.co/NveGEojy		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Dont worry bro! I h4xx0r3d the website to work via this link: http://t.co/9GJyU0IO  Good luck with your [nothing]! #confused		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I think I should write more stuff. Articles, tutorials, plotlines...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Steam. For phones. What magic is this!? http://t.co/cRPviIFQ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pineapple Smash Crew. Buy it. Play it. Enjoy it. http://t.co/BxY0F3am		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username We'll probably see some launch titles for the new xBox running UDK 4. I wouldn't be surprised if some corp's already have access.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username So far: bad, because they're not used well but as a substitute for real goals & gameplay. Design games, not achievements.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[*** BlackBerry App World Notification - Vendor Approved ***		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Latest WIP of Teddy Protector: http://t.co/oXY8bpIZ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[damn adobe and their inconsistencies
damn RIM for not having compliant sofware
damn Unity for not running on Dalvik but on Mono		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[but most of all, damn me for finding things out too late. =(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username 1 more way games are less forgiving: if you suck, you can't play any further. (first 45 sec) http://t.co/1Gzch69t		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Good luck trying to get some sleep the next couple of days. And the ones after those... and those...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Thank you, Google, for understanding what I mean when I'm too tired to type well. http://t.co/NrjcbQHD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thought I'd let you know: your game reached Kotaku http://t.co/m3BQfmJF and me and some other commenters would like to know more.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cheap gamers rejoice! http://t.co/5OUXq5cY is a Steam-like program that lists 300+ FREE games. (comparison: Steam has ~1575 games in total)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username 5 years? Where was it at that time? The earliest I can think of is in Dr. Petter's Sculptris app. http://t.co/N4s9gySL		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So... Spotify is working on an online radio service? But they can't even keep their normal servers up&running... #spotify #priorities		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Today's the 4rth time in about a month that Spotify lost its connection. You guys really need to fix server stability.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I got a 9.3/10 in http://t.co/XMsMophT . Booyah! Bow before my color-controlling cortical cones.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Built a Crush the Castle level. Now I'm a real game designer, right? http://t.co/muFhF5sa		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username NBA2K13 and Need for Speed: The Run don't have 16-player online either; does that make them bad games?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I ordered one Friday but the store had no stock. Do I still get the $25 when they get stock? After all, I 'bought' yesterday.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["@username: @username http://t.co/kXtcUNYU turbosquid's reply to someone selling my IP on their marketplace" Goddamnit, Turbosquid... Sigh.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dear Kotaku. I like you and all, but please learn the difference between parkour and freerunning. http://t.co/f96DfEBN		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["How Portal 2 Developers Became The Best 6th Grade Physics Teachers Ever http://t.co/zA896C54 " Much better than Oregon Trail.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username http://t.co/T4dEzsP0 is not one band. It's one band, and an unrelated hiphop project. They shouldn't be merged because of the name.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Do you mean Die Antwoord actually asked for it in a tweet or something, or just that they would work well as models?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Got a bit of extra work done on my sideproject, SomeHumans. Just some website mockups for now. Like? No like? http://t.co/bikeK1Dm		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pay what you want, help charity, and get 7 epic THQ games for Windows via Steam + awesome soundtracks! http://t.co/KuveKm6n SAVE THQ PEOPLE!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I just wanted to say that it's refreshing to see such big news (the chapter 11) delivered clearly and without PR lingo.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I beat the minimum and now own The Xmas Bundle 2.0 http://t.co/jLsNFiWj via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/2DObRjLu  Oooh... interesting stuff. A (linux based?) Steam console type thing.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Yay! My strip of silver finally arrived in the mail!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Just wanted to say thanks for the treasury of useful, interesting information you put out. A must-watch for every developer.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username What happened guys, did the server crash? Or are you transferring to a new host or new software or something?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Playing Guitar Hero, soundcard crashes. Finished the set list anyway. =D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Xbox is going to be the new watercooler.. wait-what? Go home Xbox, you're drunk.

http://t.co/jM1fy5VsJS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[As of today I've got over 400 games on steam... and about 100 I've never played. Never gonna get rid of this backlog am I?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hey I just saw you on KickStarter. I saw the game logo and immediately saw a cool ambigram possibility. http://t.co/ZFIy9RV77u		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I never thought I'd be amazed by tearing/crumpling paper. https://t.co/EtZhfO17tE #siggraph #3d		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Looks like Sony is 'winning' the E3 this year.
http://t.co/RCGYr4TROB

#E3 #PS4noDRM #399USdollars		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username You're aware that the vast, vast majority of the U.S. doesn't have exactly great broadband either? http://t.co/wql89Pjm23		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[2013 #noDRM Summer Sale on @username: Torchlight for FREE, 500+ Games 50% off, Daily Deals up to 90% off! http://t.co/ypzFU6U0jq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ooh, and game-sharing might be on Steam in the future... Nice! http://t.co/77YeVOfKT8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username Stayed the same? No. Gone down. http://t.co/KkTX2FmL6I Because inflation. You should know that, Mr. Bachelor's.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username If you play just the campaign, you're not buying all the DLC maps packs, are you?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Which means that if the price stays the same ($50 back then, $50 now), with less value per dollar, games are lower value/cheaper.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username We want games to be BETTER. If we go for cheap as the primary factor, we end up with clones, free-to-pay and social-exploitation.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[R.I.P. Douglas Engelbart. Father of the Mother of all Demos. We owe you so, so much.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just installed the new #Opera browser version. Dear god. ó_ò All the features are gone. It's like going from Word to Notepad. T_T		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just bought the Huawei P1 via @username. Really great deal at €204,34 (shipping included).		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is a pretty interesting game based entirely on talking:
http://t.co/GTHmkweVqO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wanna have a game out and playable by Januari. There. I've said it. It's out in the world now.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thanks for the @username article, having positive examples of games is great. Are you aware of @username's "Games for Good"?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username Uncooperative and/or slacking students make for a bad learning environment.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just bought two music CDs this week (Machinæ Supremacy and Mustasch, if you must know). That's the first time in, what, 5 years?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username A poly is several things. :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This looks like it could be an interesting series. "Fixing Blender" on GUI design http://t.co/d7F7badMA8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is some nice cross-media comic work. Read it. Read it now. (don't worry it's only five pages)
http://t.co/VXrYDlTDev		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just -almost- lost my entire site when trying to change folder organization. Thank you, universe, for hinting I should back-up more often!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Thinking about consoles in 2017. With Sony's PS4 dev tools launch games will look better, but we'll see less improvement over the lifecycle?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Well. This is dumb. If you make a bad  game, suck up the criticism and make better ones. http://t.co/AB6crKmzeD via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Not wasted time though. More like a PSA. It's good that you show us the worms in the can at times.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So far (just been using it for a month) I like @username a lot, but I don't really agree with their new pricing schemes. Mhmm...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Shit interface design: parking ticket pole sells daytickets for 3.50, or hourly rates of 1.20, I put in 3.50 and press buy. It gives 2hr55m.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cutest Deadpool cosplay? http://t.co/Xrz9qOg6Lb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wow. Dyscourse (http://t.co/eZkSPgNA5d) sounds similar to something I'm making. Down to "Oregon Trail" and "Walking Dead" as inspirations.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Might wanna look into this; Hotmail says the newsletter is shifty, I reckon many people didn't receive it. http://t.co/MWECGRPoTR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username ...this is actually one of the most convincing arguments for the xbox, assuming it lives up to what you're advertising here.		]]></document>
</author>