<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="1094e809-1306-4cd1-8ac1-ebfdf7c872b8" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[I sit with a boy in english he became my friend talking to him on Facebook i think i have a crush on him now but im not sure		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[boooored out of my mind #wannasleepbutdont		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[me and my friends are trendsetters tie our ties as bows everyone does, do a specific way of saying hi everyone does. i'm a #trendsetter		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey guys made the all nighter just woke up after falling asleep @username 8 am		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sorry wasn't on yesterday guys i was to busy partying cause yesterday was in fact my birthday. Im 14 now!! :) gosh life goes by fast.#old		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Reading a new book : The Fault In Our Stars by @username   i can kinda relate to it cause my mom died of cancer when i was 4 #goodbook		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sorry guys i havent been on but you know school sucks		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Gosh! my schools name is like super long so i always hate it when ppl ask what school i go to cause all you'll hear is blah blah blah high		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I've had the same profile pic for how long now? im gonna change it		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hahaha @username  ohhh the memories of  8th grade http://t.co/olCHIYlC0c		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[woke up this morning  to my dog liking my face Me: MAYA!! I'M TRYING TO SLEEP!!" #stupiddog		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My dad always has the A/C on in the car even when its cold and now during the heat wave it  decided to break thanks dad #notethesarcasm		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Im going to see it on friday with my freinds! I cant wait!! Untill then i'll watch BSE a thousand times :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just tweeted to @username  for a moment i thought he might see it then i refreshed the page #dontgetyourhopestohigh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Time to tweet louis 1,000 times HE WILL SEE IT :p im crazy i've always been since like 4th grade yeah who needs maturity		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username   Im going to see it on friday with my freinds! I cant wait!! Untill then i'll watch BSE a thousand times :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  I'm going to see it on friday with my freinds! I cant wait!! Untill then i'll watch BSE a thousand times :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username   Im going to see it on friday with my freinds! I cant wait! Untill then i'll watch BSE a thousand times :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Im going to see it on friday with my freinds! I cant wait!! Untill then i'll watch BSE a thousand times :p #loveyou		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Im going to see it on friday with my freinds! I cant wait!!! Untill then i'll watch BSE a thousand times :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Im going to see it on friday with my freinds! I cant wait Untill then i'll watch BSE a thousand times :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Im going to see it on friday with my freinds! I cant wait!! Untill then i'll watch BSE a thousand times :p Follow me ?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Im going to see it this week with my freinds soo exited i'll let you know how i think of it even though i know its awesome		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[There that wasnt 1,000 times but i dont want to spam him so i just did it like 10 times		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[la la la la la idk what that was dont ask im bored		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[FINALLY I FINISHED MY HOMEWORK!! #friedbrain		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you shout out the wrong answer in class with confidence		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Is it just my dentist or does everyone's dentist asks you about your life while his hands are stuffed in your mouth.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[i get told im werid alot but you know what im proud to be Wonderful Exiting Interesting Real Different!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[lol this happened to me the other day in english and im just like " just gonna keep on writing till she leaves" http://t.co/OpT3Abycdz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Normal People: I love it when mt bf/gf tells me they love me Me: I love it when my microwave tells me my food is ready #ilovefood		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When my parents sit me down and tell me its time to for me to mature Me: "Never in you wildest dreams" -Niall/ Zayn		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My life's next goal : to stop cussing  can i do it yeah i can!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Reading old messages and realizing how much i miss that person ;(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Done with my computer for tonight you guys so well good night		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hay guys, just say hi next tweet in around 30 min :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[2 hours later i post the promised 30 min tweet srry guys got caught up on homework		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[TOOO MUCH HOMEWORK  no more tweets today sorry :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  You'll wake up and have even worse morning breath then you usally have haha jk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey guys internet day!! no school for me technically! :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ugg work, im sooo tired i dont wanna do it but i got no choice		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hahahaah using google maps for my work and i  found this random fat guy next to the dumpster		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[done with my internet day FINALLY!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  wait wait wait is that the new album i thought it was were we are or is it a song OMG IM SO CONFUSED!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[sitting at home doing nothin and mabey gonna go to the movies idk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA['boat to take a shower a cold one so i can finally wake up		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Im following 777 people now thats a good number its a heavenly number to be exact		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[As you can tell i loove @username  he's hilarious and you know you live longer when you laugh so go follow him and live till your 200		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[That one best friend that turned into a stranger		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The worst feeling in the world, the one im feeling is tht knowing tht someone u used to talk to all the time doesnt care about you anymore		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[my fav color is sleep, i fold papers to my temperature, and i wonder exactly how far is Denver from america?  yeah thts right im werid!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cuts Heal, Memories Stay , Scars Pade... But im not okay #heartbroken		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Reading Freinship Quotes and immidently wanting to test my freinds to see which one is my #truefreind		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I saw you at church!!! :D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[my saturday : watch tv ,go to cross country practice, tv, church, tv bed  Oh yeah thats the life #yolo :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[i hate it when your given and assigment in english and you have no clue what to write about!! #frustrated #writersblock		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I eat alot and yet im still not fat go fast metabolism		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wake up in the morning wanting to go back to bed.... now that should be the start of Kesha's song cause i would totally relate to tht		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[you know they really shouldn't have put the w next to the e in the keyboard cause every time i want to wright how i wright hoe instead		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Behind on AGT Just saw 1D perfom started dancing and siging and then my dog just stars at me as i go " To the best song ever!"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  aww missing you too your missing alot, but im probably missing alot to I STILL WANT TO GO TO OLYMPIAN !! :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Your really going to do it? I'll be rooting for you!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[i love it when in P.E we run down the hill cause then i can throw my hands in the air and scream #fornarnia yet even when we dont i still do		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username and then i get to tell the world that i was freinds with THE Paulina Martinez!! :P  quick do  i have any pics		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[High expectations are the key to everything ! Harvard Law here I come!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Lol i would totally do that even if i dont see a baby in the relection i just dance anyways #yolo :p http://t.co/JuqB2GcByl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Unfollowing and following @username  over and over so im on the top of that list		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I will be using http://t.co/AnGdGTF7Te to manage and clean my twitter account		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I hate it when i cant sleep cause all i think about are the lucky ppl who are fast asleep		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  remember when vianney tried to throw the salami thing at me but it hit claudia http://t.co/J15J07PDCu		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#1DNoticeReiss  retweet so at least 1/5 of the boys notice reiss		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Listening to 1D of course		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[turned my head to see what my little cuz was watching on the tv BIG MISTAKE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[dont mean to brag but uh little things is about me :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[why do ppl have to be so bitchy all the time cant they just stfu and leave ppl alone		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[IM HAPPY http://t.co/KRSYpxsF5c		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Okay this thing has promblems were 100 % http://t.co/mVW0K4V4fo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nope needs to be higher http://t.co/qCmamy6H8N		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I completely disagree http://t.co/5lNnjPUmnz++		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  remember when vianney tried to throw the salami thing at me but it hit claudia http://t.co/g8cfNGLwCH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Doing geometry homework EWWWW math bleh #ihatemath		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[DONE WITH MATH now  biology yuck #ihatebio		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[gosh still not done with bio #screwhomework		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[haha finished bio now to do extra credit for guess what.. BIO!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  what? you dont believe me?:P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username haha ohhh the memories		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hi guys im bored just finished my hw YEAH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  why not? Louis wrote it for me.:P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  you seriously left the pic ?!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username of course i shouldnt have been surprised		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Friends are essential to success; they are still more essential to happiness.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My school gave me a macbook pro today hahaha good by toshiba hello apple!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  theres the one from PBL :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MAGICAL CAPE!! #thingsidoinschool Yeah im just plain cRAzY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[i want my best freind back. On the bright side we made progress today i made her laugh  #PROGRESS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  barfed and hurt his knee Me: MY BABY ARE YOU OKAY! Love ya lou hope your all right :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username lunch after everyone eats they all go lollygag leaving my group of friends with like 3 other group of friends. Then we go CrAZy #loud		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[im tired im bored soo gonna go to bed early GOOD NIGHT!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just ran around my neighborhood chasing my dog ran faster than i do in PE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[lesson in life : your dog runs fast if you want a catch him you better take a car		]]></document>
</author>