<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="1d2a2248-1dbf-4e18-933d-42eeedb3ae7e" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[@username -Don't ever let anyone accuse you of NOT being a DEEP THINKER!  Now, any thoughts on the fiscal cliff we r speeding toward?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username - tough Chick!!!!!  2012 Conference Carolinas Championship - Chrissy Melcher, "The Speech": http://t.co/ixSgQItF via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[GO @username! Amazing Week for Mocs - Grapple at the Garden Promo | Video | Flowrestling http://t.co/2PZH5m78 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username - Way to go, @username - and THANKS for great updates for those of us that couldn't be there!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hearings? No time!  Our Pres is too busy covering up Fast & Furious details, not to mention murdering our own in Benghazi		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Please Support the son of a Grassland Teacher-- a Recently Handicapped Graduate Student's Research in Nuclear Fusion  http://t.co/BeqXqWtK		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Oh No!!!!  Can you go back to dr?  You should be feeling better by now!  Hurry-Santa's coming<3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Yay!  You should be well in plenty of time for Santa ... and all that coal isn't gonna dig itself out of your stocking, you know		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Guns kill people" so let's ban guns.  Ok. I get that Logic.  Let's stop Rape while we are at it too... what to ban?...what to ban?....		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username SO SAD & If banning or controlling guns will end shooting deaths-Do It!  While we are at it, can we Stop Rape too?  Same Way		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username What a great week for you guys and your fans!  Congratulations, Mr. Soto, on Being #CHATTANOOGASTRONG		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Incredible #southernscuffle -thanks @username for exciting, fast-paced, crazy,wall-to-wall, intense, perfect event! Thank you, ATHLETES!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey! @username  Am I wearing pants? http://t.co/FHdkEL3t via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[WAY TO GO @username - YOU ARE A BEAST!! Congratulations - LOTS of love from Franklin, TN right now!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username That IS a sweet roomie & thanks for the fashion tip printed on top of list!  I always count on you girls to keep me in-the-know.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I love you anyway!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/LQGBE9a9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username let's do that!!!!!  5 hour countdown for me- then I can start planning our PIU!!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username so excited that I made a list of what to bring for so much fun!!! PROBLEM-my LiSt won't fit in car!! 
Let the good times roll!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I was just going to invite you to go with K and me to a wrestling tournament this weekend.  Do you know anybody else I could ask?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[GREAT DAY! Celebrating the Past & TAKING CARE OF BUSINESS TODAY @username 22, Citadel 20. Congrats-all #GOMOCS wrestlers, coaches, fans!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username -Thank you for week of forever-happy memories! You are the Hostest with the Mostest AND the #BestDaughter in the world! I LOVE YOU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username I want..John to call- tell me EVERYTHING about his life, hopes, dreams, feelings-& that secretly he's homesick 4 me!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Great Monday Moc Talk today! @username -All Business as Usual, but he almost seemed...happy?? #NoWay http://t.co/RtiSW06H		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username yes, sir.  might not be what you want- but I actually have 2 - I think both perfect and not being used.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username WOW!  So proud to be a CHATTANOOGA WRESTLING fan.  Taking care of business, on AND off the mat. Way to go, MOCS!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username How is the most beautiful girl at UTC today???  If you are anything less than happy -I'm coming over there!!!!  I'll do it!  ilu		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[GREAT Open letter to IOC from Donald @username @username Wrestling voted out of Olympics? Yes-just UNBELIEVABLE! #SaveOlympicWrestling		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/aBP08Zoy Report on @username guys in new rankings NCAA D-1. Go @username! Go @username! Go @username!  and MORE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So good to see this boy!! AND 3 more just like him! @username @username @username M.Lopez   #happymom http://t.co/V3QoXOqF		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username SO LOVED having you this weekend and getting to know you!! Now, STOP BLOWING UP TWITTER OR I'LL BE FORCED TO UNFOLLOW U-CHILL!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Teen angst.  It's a terrible thing to let go to waste.  Keep it up, Jack :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Best of Brand Spotlight: University of Tennessee at Chattanooga Sharpens Direction with Mission and… http://t.co/dRKUUWNOKt via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username James shared this w/me-too real-he's honest. MACKLEMORE- OTHERSIDE REMIX FEAT. FENCES: http://t.co/j6tLX3oW7m via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username - I think this is it!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username National Collegiate Open wrestling   Arthur Ashe Center, Richmond · http://t.co/2ngjy3fV9l		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I knew you would love it- the whole album is just beautiful! Be careful though- don't get #BeiberFever!!! @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my favorite wrestling team in the country, @username, on a great day today #TakingCareOfBusiness.  GO MOCS!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thanks for helping show world that wrestlers aren't block-heads, but scholars & def. not suffering from head injuries at all!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I have Been ready - I hope YOU are ready!  Try to keep up with #Gigi and #KidRock!  See you soon, #K-Rock!!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I love you!!!!!  Your visit made my my day and trip!! We are So Much Alike #soulmates #coolgirls - I hope 2 see again SOON!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username What else could we do???  Wish you were here - #OnlyThingThatWouldMakeItBetter  #bffs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Isn't it sad and amazing the incredible people we miss out on because we label them just "that 22 yr old nanny" or whatever else?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username eh.  I never read all of yours to me anyway.  They were funny, sure, but a tad monotonous.  (NEW SPECIAL IS AWESOME!!!)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Mocs win Third Straight SoCon Title with FOUR CHAMPS! Exciting day online-GRT job, @username! #ChattanoogaMocs #ILoveUTCwrestling		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username -Congratulations on your Big SoCon win today and for qualifying for NCAA's!  #ChattanoogaStrong #IloveChattanoogawrestling		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username GO, NIKO!!!  Awesome job today taking SoCon Title -See you at the NCAA's!!!!!  #ChattanoogaStrong #IloveChattanoogaWrestling		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username He's a Beast! -I bet he sees what we saw too - his Daddy pacing in the background!  No wonder he's not relaxing in that tub:)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username "kick butt and give Glory to God"......If that's not a famous Southern wrestling saying - it should be!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#d1wrestle, Baby!  Getting pumped for NCAA Championships next week. #RESPECT to every man there-ESPECIALLY my @username guys! #Represent		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username You can take the boy out of the country..... but, yeah, no, you can't.  They'll just find it wherever they are!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Watching for GREAT things from you next week #d1wrestle - NCAA's-can't wait! - Congratulations and just Go #ChattanoogaStrong!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I KNOW YOU ARE! So many of us there- #d1wrestle, #NCAA's- - every minute in spirit-watching - cheering XXLoud from Tennessee!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Do not fear-do not be dismayed; I am your God. I will strengthen you & help you; I will uphold you with my righteous right hand—Isaiah 41:10		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username What WILL stop you?  I only ask because SO many people want to know!!!!  I love you, Parker and I know the answer is "nothing"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username -So excited to hear from JB! -headed to grocery store-hope they are stocked!  What are your favorite meals? #yay		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Great MM Talk with Coach E! Thanks Coaches & Seniors!!! #WeLoveOurMocs #WeBelieve  http://t.co/3fqnJwuEV2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  Last chance to place orders!  You know you boys are in the south now and can order fried chicken and biscuits :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username Sounds good!  Doing my part to keep our boys #ChattanoogaStrong !!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Just got notice you are now following me. You weren't ALREADY?? Your biggest fan? Your own Mom? I'm considering blocking you...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username So happy to have you here! You liked my southern cooking enough to even say"Thank Y'all"! Grt visit!!! http://t.co/S42zCmEkFs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I am sure they were all great.... but I hope you spotted a few who are #ChattanoogaStrong!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I just proved Oreo cookies as delicious at 39,500 ft- headed to Vegas for wrestling nationals! Won't be updating~~-what happens in Vegas....		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username banquet 6:30-can't wait! Leaving now b/c @username told us 22 hrs ago he needed to move today :)Are you ready for this, KF?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[20 things to start doing in your personal relationships.... I think I will!! -  http://t.co/oyRFnVeQLB via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username Finally paroled from 8th grade today!  Off to GMS to "recognize" you and celebrate w/you! Good Job, Boys! #ilu		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Akron, Ohio-University Nationals-Ready to see our @username Boys Wrestle!  #GoMocs!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Last 2 days to vote for Coach Rocco! 10 seconds to show our respect #ChattanoogaStrong <3 our coaches! http://t.co/u4OTyqdPLr		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Coach E!  When will Mr Hooker have Twitter (I remember you encouraging a couple of Fr last year), so we can congratulate him?!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username You are quickly becoming my main reason to remember to check Twitter!  #That'sFunnyIDontCareWhoYouAre #MyNephew		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Heard "summer wrestling makes winter champions"-seen it's true-Yay!!! for teachers who are willing to "train" off-season! #GoBurros		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Takes one to know one.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username - this made me think of you!!!  And welcome home, @username !!!!!  Good to know Karen has you for a while <3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username -somehow made me think of you!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username Cam, you misspelled PERFECT - - and I totally agree with you!!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username BEST TWEET EVER!!!!!  <3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username MY HERO! I'm sorry for snake, but 1 of us had to go! The snake & I were CRAZY- Jack stayed cool as usual http://t.co/ZwtJMCGBfa		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Caden is SO happy Uncle John-John is home!  She is a HUGE @username fan, but is happy to have @username home!! http://t.co/ZSRHCCr4jR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Boooooooo!  I actually wasted time feeling sad - complete with very sad face -on your tweet!!  #TEENAGERS!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#itrustthegovtlike I trust teenagers and 2 year olds.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  Watch out for the CHUPACABRA!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username This tweet makes me need to watch Napoleon Dynamite... no reason.  That's not until Sept so Relax and make yourself a quesa-dilla		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username jack made a new friend this week http://t.co/Ylv41beueK		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username - you 2 are having ENTIRELY too much fun in Puerto Rico! Be careful - #chupacabra http://t.co/9mhb61lvlS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Kid Dynamite Vs. World's Greatest | 2013 World Team Trials | Flowrestling http://t.co/4fT1WGt1Y3 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  @username  DOWN TO DAKE VS BURROUGHS! "What's it like to wrestle best in the world?" Dake: "I am the best in the world".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MS/HS WRESTLERS: TN St Champ Camp @username BGA,coached by @usernameJShrader184  @usernameawoody141  @usernameMcCoy_Newberg @usernameparkjaysmith next 2 wks! http://t.co/evcZnsRCNA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Mark Munoz-If Anderson Silva Doesn’t Want a Rematch with Weidman, He’d like One -  http://t.co/SiRUTwKW98 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username - How is  INTENSIVE CAMP going??  We are hearing big things! Could you ask @username why he's called dad 2x & mom ZERO?! <3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Would you mind terribly waiting until right after my funeral to use the word "twerk" again?  Oh, also maybe "Miley" too! ha		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username I never ? our coaches, but this explains dancing practice at summer camp-U never know when you might NEED it!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Was it this Shady GUY??????? http://t.co/8pcbbpgPgo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hey #NinjaTrainer, Question from friend-is there Ninja camp next week?  If so-what day/s and times?  Thanks!  #IWantToBeANinja		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Buying some red/gray Rulons for your beast little bro- @username - He starts High School in 14 days.  #GoRebels #HappyBoy		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username oops- Red/Black		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Papaw, Thanks for buying me this tutu and purple glitter polish in NOLA! Welcome home- i love you! @username http://t.co/HwYKUpFz8x		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey @username It's official #RattyFreshman ready for high school!  #NewWrestlingShoes @username @username http://t.co/7J476msRRA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  @username CAN'T STOP DANCING SINCE UTC CAMP! These are exact shoe @username wore jr/sr year-big FIND on Ebay!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[NCAA Champ Ellis Named Mocs Assistant -WOW!- WELCOME COACH ELLIS AND congrats @username http://t.co/L3UpfTciQt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Doesn't matter any way... after 25 years I think you are stuck with me!!!  love, deb  @username @username http://t.co/DN6QzVBMkV		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Welcome Back, Hillsboro!: http://t.co/9hKZAz8EnP via @username  @username - how awesome - I want to go to Hillsboro High School!!!		]]></document>
</author>