<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="2298a7cc-0672-4f32-b2af-6ca358c20a7f" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[Life is too short and you never know what will happen. Treasure your friends and family.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[In shock. A very dear friend died last night unexpectedly. RIP Steve.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[God...you never expect something like this to happen. I don't even know what to do with myself.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Please help support Steven Collison's funeral fund. Melina Ann, Logen Shawn Pierce, Ronda Riley, Laurie Acosta,... http://t.co/Kz33YHKo8t		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Check it out! I am helping Steve Collison's Funeral Fund --please help--this is a local #STL family from #FloMo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is my very dear friend--please help me help his family http://t.co/apnm7NjGt3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is my dear friend and my husband's best friend. His wife is my best friend and she needs help. Please help... http://t.co/JYQrzsdgsZ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm raising money for Steve Collison's Funeral Fund . Click to Donate: http://t.co/GPs4yXSuXE #gofundme		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Influence Marketing campaign strategies for Brands http://t.co/z6kmEhytKp via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Influence Marketing Campaign Strategies For Brands http://t.co/dagfJIKzvy via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#stl please help this grieving local family who lost their fathet/husband this weekend #donate -  http://t.co/VTYJyCD8t6		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Random Thoughts from a Tangled Mind Excerpt: Chapters in Life http://t.co/0pxLSBJ9Yd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Random Thoughts from a Tangled Mind Excerpt: Chapters in Life http://t.co/KTawSjIT41		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Stats for the week have arrived. 5 new followers and 8 unfollowers via http://t.co/Efw9cgs9xt.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why and How to Keep Your Blood Sugar in Check - http://t.co/qFSli2mukl via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Healthy unconditional love requires a bonding beyond the surface appearance and behaviour of someone. It’s a... http://t.co/o8fxIfGKw1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HELP US TO HELP LEAH!!!  http://t.co/EOMxooVFGg via @username #STL #DONATE #CHARITY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[38-year-old #STL dad passes away unexpectedly, family struggles to pay for funeral #DONATE #CHARITY http://t.co/zjj6kd4Ffu via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Here's some additional info about Steve and the family: http://t.co/LEvVssHZ5E... http://t.co/GPs4yXSuXE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Here's some additional info about Steve and the family: http://t.co/JQzw0d93JT http://t.co/bPhsi8ZiuH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wow--take it to heart. http://t.co/LWfODdXqgU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Op-Ed: CES 2014: Tech firms bet on miniaturized audio systems http://t.co/HtTNgjplu4 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bill Atkinson and I just enjoyed Noah's concert before heading to dinner, where we met a lady who had fallen on... http://t.co/8Z5PilWKrb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I am so thankful to everyone who has donated and shared so far! Thank you all from the bottom of my heart... http://t.co/GPs4yXSuXE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I am so thankful to everyone who has donated and shared so far! Thank you all from the bottom of my heart for... http://t.co/tBQJ5dqr5k		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Random Thoughts from a Tangled Mind Excerpt: Chapters in Life http://t.co/BaWn2FUT2j		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Random Thoughts from a Tangled Mind Excerpt: Chapters in Life http://t.co/yxxqrzIhd0		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Some things change you forever.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Here are the funeral arrangements for our friend Steven Collison for those who want the info. http://t.co/VtVrfDmRgZ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You would smile if you saw your knuckles tonight, Steven.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I donated to Steve Collison's Funeral Fund  http://t.co/GPs4yXSuXE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who has donated so far! We have reached $1,125 so far toward Steve's funeral cost. Plea... http://t.co/GPs4yXSuXE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who has donated so far! We have reached $1,125 so far toward Steve's funeral cost. Please... http://t.co/UwNTR2xPcR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Having trouble focusing this week but grateful for the ability to shell out a few extra bucks to pay an awesome... http://t.co/KxvvkHKZ1R		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Our friend's visitation was tonight. I was shocked that someone attempted to start pointless drama...but justice... http://t.co/fqGTOaitg7		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Aww. That's probably sadly true. :( http://t.co/r6G0iDTIwx		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Almost to Mexico to bury Steven Collison. I can't believe this is really happening. — feeling sad		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Always funny when people pretend to know someone just because they share a little DNA. To today's little drama... http://t.co/Xf0IIXJocw		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My week on twitter: 1 New Followers, 3 Mentions, 21K Mention Reach, 3 Replies, 4 Retweets, 67.9K Retweet Reach. via https://t.co/Yp3koy4me3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Peace, love and doves. It's a new day.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A red beret with a Gap jacket and my #PeopleVIP leopard print scarf. Love or hate the look? http://t.co/Z6MWLRbPxb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I am stepping into my drama-free bubble again. Life must go on and I'd prefer that it does so in a positive way.... http://t.co/0iCcDXF9Wa		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Feel like I've been in some twisted type of suspended animation. Tomorrow is a day for cleaning out my closets.... http://t.co/hEB1KXVvWu		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Being diplomatic would seem like a good thing, but when you also have a conscious and the ability to empathize,... http://t.co/bEbZrRT6qF		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm cleaning out my closet. Just like this...except my own coffee. I prefer it to Starbucks anyway lol! Who's... http://t.co/cJAR6H3eSq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[OK I am not a football person...but holy schmolies this halftime show is rocking my world!! Bruno Mars and Red... http://t.co/tD56MkQOIy		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thanks ;)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thanks for sharing! You're now featured on http://t.co/9vNtbzaeNP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google's purchase of Nest raises privacy concerns http://t.co/CFJYQ8r1Qm via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My Klout Score is 63. Join me on Klout to discover yours today. http://t.co/OaTEgrM4kr		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[New social network aims for real-time connections http://t.co/2azcfntqfN via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Where are they now? Facebook founders have wide impact http://t.co/g8R6LaZh1W via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Do you prefer FB over Twitter? http://t.co/v6F39aheuh via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google and Nest--should you be concerned? http://t.co/MEhcQbItBb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thanks for sharing! You're now featured on http://t.co/9vNtbzaeNP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[FAA grounds flying beer drone; cites lack of legal precedent http://t.co/ziRaTFysVX via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Beer drones? Maybe not... http://t.co/k7FmItTPr7		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No beer drones for you! http://t.co/7F9b19b8gX		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google's purchase of Nest raises privacy concerns http://t.co/6n89GMxpEk via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Top Posts from January 2014 http://t.co/7M2x9ct4sG		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Top Posts from January 2014 http://t.co/NKlE24MIos		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How to Attract Influencers: A Guide for Brands  http://t.co/oSKKHoMiaW via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm in a Nine Inch Nails kind of mood...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Top Posts from January 2014 http://t.co/fHH3vhsvjS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Top Posts from January 2014 http://t.co/j9hTYWepsE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How To Promote Your Next Influence Marketing Campaign http://t.co/YsKOx5ODJE via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[OK. Today is an Eminem kinda day. I'm gonna lose myself in the music (of my work). Here we go...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[8 tweeps followed (thank you!) and 5 unfollowed (goodbye!) me in the past week. Thank you http://t.co/Efw9cgs9xt.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Actions Speak Louder Than Words http://t.co/qKdQdrbLNl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Actions Speak Louder Than Words http://t.co/PrA16q2Qlw		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[She's GORGEOUS! And a so-called "plus-size" model. I think we have the same body haha...except she's probably got... http://t.co/yZoHabQyIQ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Changing the Curve: Ivory May Kalber, Top Model and Television Personality - http://t.co/tbhyhhAkF5 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why and How to Keep Your Blood Sugar in Check - http://t.co/qFSli2mukl via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Meet Eric Kelly, Olympic and Golden Glove boxer - http://t.co/mdur7qsweN via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No Excuses: Personal Trainer Says You Can Get Fit in 12 Minutes a Day (Video) - http://t.co/QAO81ybCpi via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Be Like Tyson Beckford: Follow Me on Twitter - http://t.co/cckVffT1rC via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Study: A Low-Fat Diet Could Prevent Cancer, Heart Disease - http://t.co/pCsnaV9wPd via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sleep: Why You Need It and How to Get It - http://t.co/766bHZ26fs via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A Personal Fitness Trainer on Competitive Bodybuilding - http://t.co/LA80yAZaws via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Body Fat Percentage is The Right Way to Measure Fitness - http://t.co/EAlrZDKUTt via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Google's Purchase Of Nest Raises Privacy Concerns: http://t.co/e8vJY5thiO (via @username and @username) #scroogled		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Actions Speak Louder Than Words http://t.co/OxDJkjVKdj		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Actions Speak Louder Than Words http://t.co/0n6gIXs616		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Today's philosophy: stand in your light and speak your truth.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Brickbuster: The Lego Movie really snaps together - http://t.co/pGSUiEGxRa via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Announcing the All-New St. Louis Observer http://t.co/g0fHPOeoOg #STL #NEWS #Blog30 #blogboost		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Change Your Life: ItWorks! CEO Mark Pentecost on 'Re-Dreaming' - http://t.co/mJioOxPdz4 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Have you tried that crazy wrap thing? - http://t.co/k7C6rzQpFs via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Like my new page? http://t.co/PjugZILZ7B		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Have you tried that Crazy Wrap Thing? http://t.co/MLspENHpY3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Change Your Life: ItWorks! CEO Mark Pentecost on ‘Re-Dreaming’ http://t.co/a32VD2F0A9 on @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Have you tried that crazy wrap thing? http://t.co/XobfnWPAjJ on @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Change Your Life: ItWorks! CEO Mark Pentecost on ‘Re-Dreaming’ http://t.co/pGESBt8XOP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Change Your Life: ItWorks! CEO Mark Pentecost on ‘Re-Dreaming’ http://t.co/Wpy2sH8cNB		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Have you tried that crazy wrap thing? http://t.co/4tH4RQLyG1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Have you tried that crazy wrap thing? http://t.co/2qewq8jc9c		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Autopsy reveals more questions than answers in Phillip Seymour Hoffman case http://t.co/8GTbzfXPey via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Phillip Seymour Hoffman's death is more of a mystery than ever. RIP Philip Seymour Hoffman http://t.co/cjFGnDtiaJ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is so sad. http://t.co/9RdkKYMc1g		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Kids and I just put pineapple upside down cake in the oven. Turn up! LOL :)		]]></document>
</author>