<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="4e165fb2-3dac-413a-a38d-696737dd775b" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[Mike Kestemont in "Hildegard of Bingen: Authorship and Stylometry" http://t.co/W4bsE7TV88 #digitalhumanities #authorshipattribution		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[An Aspiring Scientist’s Frustration with Modern-Day Academia: A Resignation http://t.co/7paTZSaQiU via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I'll do my best :-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If you have an idea, sharing it with me does not reduce its utility to you but usually increases it. (1/2)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[In fact, in order to realize their maximum productivity, ideas, images, and affects must be common and shared. (Hardt, 2010, p. 349). (2/2)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bealls lijst van criminele open access publishers, om te bookmarken: http://t.co/CkCQEjMTgY via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[TwiNL: A deeper understanding of society. http://t.co/rQeGOEM39N via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Used a metaphor over the phone lately? The IARPA metaphor program, running since 2011  http://t.co/U5aFppVOXY #metaphor #iarpa		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Big Data Brain Drain: Why Science is in Trouble http://t.co/LQqCfHxXM8 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Japanese teens spend more time online than watching tv; they also read more textual content than older generations #socinfo13		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Yet, youths show sharp decrease in interest in politics, intolerance towards opposing views. Keynote by prof Yoshiaki Hashimoto #socinfo13		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/uAP7HlTF3c browser plugin suggests news articles from different perspectives. Paul Resnick keynote #socinfo13		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @username & Björn Burscher for their SocInfo2013 best paper award! #socinfo13 http://t.co/jYbVMOez0Q		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username I'd start with Chinese movies involving food talk - then use English subtitles as pivot food words		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Go on an help to create searchable text from scanned historical documents! http://t.co/GEzVhQroMU #WLT		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Net7's @username presents @username at @username meeting - great OS tool for enriching dighum data with semantically structured annotations		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username: technology is like salt - you don't eat a full plate of salt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username talking DH @username meeting - go beyond standard NLP pipeline, towards knowledge discovery. MITCH revived! http://t.co/SbrCJzDvhj		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/upRj6R34Y2 - great application for visualizing actor social networks in novels by CrossLibrary #dhfbk2013		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[New minor E-Humanities at Radboud University - http://t.co/yhvsFx6DDg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Looking at Culture through a Big Data Lens http://t.co/YMOn09eVRU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[always nice to see old demos still working: Implicit Linguistics - Constructicon Demo http://t.co/kCDHRG2vnR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[? Trans Canada Highway – Boards of Canada http://t.co/vjKTIPa9Vr #NowPlaying		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[social media fuels violent teen mobs in Florida & New York  http://t.co/TYlg903H8H via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[New clues for unlocking the Voynich manuscript? http://t.co/RxGCcPbqsf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Filosofen-G8 agenda 3: Information overload? http://t.co/fiJwWBkYF1 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[America Has a New Language  http://t.co/tGe7G1S0jD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Gnip and Twitter Bringing Social Data to Academic Researchers http://t.co/1Jlif2w43u via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Eight (No, Nine!) Problems With Big Data http://t.co/9ni1W8eqXN		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[impressive presentation by James Jardine at #eacl2014 - topical pagerank of scientific papers, built into Qiqqa -  http://t.co/SmExUdANys		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username #volkskrant: Oeps. 'Duck you Smedley', tweette Paypal-topman Agrawal. Nu is hij ontslagen. http://t.co/wbhpGfEiI2”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A Billion Words: Because today's language modeling standard should be higher http://t.co/FOHajhRZFs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Academics Anonymous: why I'm leaving academia http://t.co/OXM9dzqhDK		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Unpaid social media prosumers: modern slaves? Digital Labour and Karl Marx http://t.co/H4oO2sswyd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Free online course on data journalism: https://t.co/ZMxTPJQHx7 #MOOC		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[KNAW Computational Humanities + IBM White Paper: Meaning and Perspectives in the Digital Humanities https://t.co/HCrfJNeGbe		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Organized links to publicly available code and data - cheers to @username and ACL community! Now let's expand this  http://t.co/39w2ldpLcP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#nanopubs: also interesting for digital humanities? Open Humanities Award for early modern peace treaties http://t.co/MOWQZCrQxm		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Artists condenses cultural history into five-minute video http://t.co/uqbpm8WmtC		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A global guide to the first world war - interactive documentary - http://t.co/RuFr6MlarY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Dan Jurafsky: The Language of Food: A Linguist Reads the Menu http://t.co/Pe4ZCBjaFL via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Faces of Science: Florian Kunneman @username @username http://t.co/nbTumgQKvC  #facesofscience		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[First million Coursera words translated into Russian by ABBYY crowdsourcing project http://t.co/1KubuVh3LH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[For Big-Data Scientists, ‘Janitor Work’ Is Key Hurdle to Insights http://t.co/hkHbmG1ZRc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Proceedings of the CoNLL workshop series from 1997 now in the main listing of the ACL Anthology http://t.co/HiNeSa6gab #conll		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Our webservices running on CLAM, revamped, by @username - http://t.co/pp9eMSG41o		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username FIDO, Freedom of Information Document Overview: http://t.co/ETyR1UncaH powered by @username @username - in Dutch		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["There is no such thing as information overload": About 83,100 results on Google.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hosting research data together with bittorrent technology -
http://t.co/VEqzaDreZB		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Workshop SUBTIEL 'SUBTItles for Every Linguist', 17 Dec http://t.co/68jTA57HPg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Workshop MERIT 'Machine-based Extraction of Relations In Texts' 15 Dec http://t.co/PwZyAQjlfi		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[a norm = anticipation of sanctions. Definition by Heinrich Popitz. Christian Gudehus, "understanding human actions" at #MERIT workshop		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Path-finding projects at Netherlands eScience Center: applications for funding now open 
https://t.co/nPDLrDjIvh #nlesc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Published: CLIN journal article on Basilex, 11.5M words, texts for children http://t.co/PYPKlsxG4c http://t.co/6bKR7zRPxr #languagemachines		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Published: T-Scan: a new tool for analyzing Dutch text, in CLIN Journal http://t.co/eINoyC9laP powered by CLAM, Frog, WOPR #languagemachines		]]></document>
</author>