<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="57c6c6f0-1989-4fe1-895e-1be3194aaf3b" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[I hate it when people stand in the middle of the hall that everyone walks by and they start having a deep conversation and wont move.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Haven't been sleeping well, which is ridiculous cuz I have decades of experience		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Naming my law firm/night club "Mullet." People will have to walk through the business in the front to get to the party in the back.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I before E except when you run a feisty heist on a weird beige foreign neighbor.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If i ever created a social network the password must include a capital letter, a number, a plot, a protagonist, and and a twist ending		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I hate when people think that just cause i'm a tomboy i cant like guys well new flash i'm in love w/ @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  I'll tell you tomorow and i wasn't really mad at you i had to take it out on someone and you were right there so i'm sorry		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  #97 you think Mr.Ong's nose is cute well actually you think everyone's nose is cute		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'M FAAAAAMOS!! My name was on the CST except it said he in the second sentence :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Not feelin to well  today (emotinally)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  #96  I can always trust you and if theres any problem i could always come to you.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  # 95 :  We completely understand each others weirdness		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Congardulations @username  i have finally decided to do the 100 thingamabob for you		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  OOOPS hehehe congratulation not whatever i put there		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  #100  we both have awesome dance moves		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just made a bacon pizza cant wait to eat		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  what are you talking about paulina i make you laugh everyday		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  actually the correct grammar would be if u ever have done the CST then you understand the pain i'm going through.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  hahahahah sorry i just had to go tutor mode on you		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If we didnt have school on mondays we would all hate tuesdays so lets all say thank you to monday because tuesday doesn't deserve hate		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  #94: Were Both Blind		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I will read my horoscope from as many different sources as I need to until I find the one I like		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Has anyone ever had a friend tht was more like there sister, and then suddenly she wasnt your friend anymore then you know how i feel		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#imagine that your having a crappy birthday when one direction comes to your party and sings your favorite song by them and Louis kisses you		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[YES!!! LAST DAY OF CST TESTING!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[srry i havent been on in awhile just eneded the cst's and i already  got a crap load of  work		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When im just havin a hella of a good time with my friends #ItsAllGood		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  and @username  are at my house!!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[never and i mean never let @username  walk into your house hahaahhaha jk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username # 93: Were Both Deaf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  is stupid and a dog		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username yeah but it was random		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[fine @username  you win i'll tell the whole world that i can rap. there i did it happy now.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[helping hannah on her math homework cause im awesome		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[if i drink alcohol, I am an alcoholic, but if i drink fanta then.....I am FANTASTIC!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[when you're thinking of someone does that mean there thinking of you to?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I HATE SCIENCE!! right after they gave us a project they give us another one and there both soooo confusing!!!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username ahhhhh poopy during my rehearsals i wasnt able to take of pic of my #wonderful acting skills		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username i'm not afraid of all the attention so how come i'm so #afraidoftalking to her (#shesnotafraid) http://t.co/anL8DCiCPK		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[had my play today #toystory3 it was a full house and at the end a little girl asked me for my autograph!!!!!! #imabefamous one day!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[gotta stay #upallnight havent even started my algebra project thats due tommorow... after i sleep from now to 12 GOOD NIGHT!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  look whatever the hell i did how much you wanna bet i didnt mean it. I dont wanna to relive the jessica thing im sorry		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Every Year @username this time of year i #loseafriend so through out the day i'll tweet who they are and what happened		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Kinder - Ana - i cant remember what but i know it was something i said		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[1st grade- Emily- i said " no one likes you anymore "		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[2nd- Rebecca- I told her i was smarter than her , Idk 2nd graders are werid		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[3rd - Samantha- I told her she was a butt face (tht words has always been in my vocab)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[4th- Bethany- I pushed her off the play structure		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[5th- Alexis - she broke my boyfriends neck (well current x-boyfriend)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[6th- Angela- its a long story		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[7th- Jessica- she started dating my brother so we had a falling out and this is the one out of all of them that hurts the most		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[8th (current) - @username - Idk she wont tell me and if your reading this paulina read all my tweets first to understand		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A #realfriend will forgive you no matter what you do so i dont give a shit if @username  doesn't fucking forgive me, #shenotafriend		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Scared as hell for Friday, Thursday i don't care but Friday WISH ME LUCK!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[i need to pee ... yes i am not afraid to tell the world that cause thats #whoiam		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/CqiuHyY1Qo  I feel  like this for 2 people that friendship that i ruined and didn't know what i did :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I HAVE 111 TWEETS !!!! THATS LIKE A PERFECT NUMBER!! awwww now i have 112 :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[FINALLY I CLEARED MY E-MAIL!! that thing was a mess, now for my backpack....wish me luck i found a sock in there once XD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username YAAAY!!! we have backpacks that eat thing ohhh but your socks are cool :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  youll find out know woncha		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hahahahaha suckers i don't got school today or tommorow :P  but seriously i dont!! how exciting.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  I DON'T HAVE SCHOOL TODAY!!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just got back from my service learning presentation WE GOT 100% YEAH!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username cracks me up with her youtube videos		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My last day of middle school so sad :( on the bright side i got out 1 week earlier XD !!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Lots of hugging went  on today cant believe i hugged them back !!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Me when i meet one direction http://t.co/3kjOXIv2z9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I GRADUATED!!!! IM A BIG KID NOW!!!! HIGH SCHOOL HERE I COME		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[went to a party yesterday cause i graduated was fun but then at the end everyone was crying cause were never going to see each other again		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hey sorry i haven't been on I've been training to be a junior life guard		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[WTF IS THIS!!! THIS GUY CANT GO AROUND SAYING THT WERE NOT A COUNTRY!! #icantbeliveit   http://t.co/OJd5Hjtsia		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[OMG   I HAVE 100 FOLLOWERS !! THTS NOT ALOT BUT STILLL EXITED !!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I am sooo happy today!!!  I am lost of words :D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username   hahaha louis your so funny and awesome!!! I love you!!! not in that creepy stalker way though :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[watch  @username  videos  and subscribe to her cause shes just tht awesome!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Yesterday i got stung by a giant jelly fish and almost drowned see going to the beach everyday for the junior lifeguard isnt tht fun		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  No we should be thanking you guys cause you let us see you guys and your #fabuLOUIS and hear your #amaZAYN music		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[really sorry i havent been on you guys since ive been doin the junior lifeguards thing i come home soooo tired		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[when my names on a math problem everyone stares at me and im like yeaaaah i can drive 2 miles   that mean i got my licences		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[goood bye from twitter for ever @username  i'll miss you  and sadly never talk to you agian... see ya when school starts :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  idk i dont thnink so IM SOO CONFUSED!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  see dont ya get it my name was in the cst and i was driving remeber		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[tommorow i have to swim 1000 Yards and run 2 miles for the junior lifeguard thing who thinks i can do it! #wishmeluck		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username OMG!!!!! you posted this 2 months before my B-day its a sign its meant to be your gonna be my husband  :D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My favorite color is blue .... idk im just werid like tht		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Went to aquatica today w/ my junior lifeguard freinds		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Do a little more each day than you think you possibly can." - Lowell Thomas		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  " Surfers, south of the truck!"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Cherish your visions and your dreams, as they are the children of your soul,  the blueprints of your ultimate accomplishments" - Napoleon H		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  All your songs are the best songs ever :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  YEAH!!  ooooh but thts cause your going to a diffrent high school :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username Oh please my Mt. Jelly was waaaay better than tht :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  its sandy the sandman i would know i named it and then ditched you guys to make Mt. Jelly :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Yeah you guys really wanted to make a sandman but Mt. Jelly was better we didn't even get judged! #toocoolforjudges		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Yesterday one direction released there new song best song ever!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username i need to tell you something its the reason i refused to let go of Voldemort		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Its a choice, not a chance, that determines your destiny" - Jean N		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[That moment in life when you keep waiting for something tht you know wont happen		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Lol just watched the new music vid from one direction i cant stop laughing!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Louis your even sexy when your a fat old man :)		]]></document>
</author>