<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="5a3757da-1eda-4bb5-bf68-816fa10c2231" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[When paths cross		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The term to best describe the speed at which I do things is definitely haul ass.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Now we play the wait for my stop game		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Think I might be changing my bus route		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Organize and alphabetize all day #worktweet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I never meant to hurt anyone, I just didn't want to hurt anymore either.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The lonely stoner seems to free her mind at night.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck the past few days.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I could really go for some coffee right now, but I think I'll settle for a bowl instead		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Yeah? You too pal!" Could be one of my catch phrases #brooklynborn		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Toll bridge trolls need to eat too.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Today the paychecks come in, and even though I can't deposit until tomorrow morning, I can't fucking wait!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Seems like I should have my #jawboneup back finally!! Boo yah!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Upgrading my room		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[She always calls right when I'm getting ready to leave for work -.-		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Lol, word? Aight then.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Shaken my ass while I hit the bong, cause it makes me feel so damn good		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[There's still some hood rat in me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Time to slip on something a little more comfortable and hit the bong.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Don't need saving, cause there's no salvation for a bad girl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[3and a half hours till I can get back to where I wanna be.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cabin in the Woods. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck yes to this movie. Simply that. Fuck yes.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#Elysium was pretty cool ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Oh my god, I wish I could figure out what I did to my left shoulder/arm, cause it hurts like a motherfucker!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I hate these games....		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Do what you will.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Looks like I'll be taking the bus a lot more		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Woke up to some static and stress  rewind. Think Im'a wake up to a bowl instead.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username see, what he had meant to say is "when a Child is bad" but what he Had said is "when a Person is bad"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ey!! Neighborhood rules apply!! You ain't seen nuthen, you ain't heard nuthen, you don't know nuthen. #thingsisayatwork		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Over the hills and far away, she prays that he'll return someday. 
As sure as the river meets the sea, back in his arms he swears she'll be		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nothing to do for the next hour		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When you don't even get a goodbye and you don't hear from someone all day <<		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I guess they realized I don't have shit to do either so they sent me home early. Right after my bus left.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So now I'm waiting 20 minutes for the next bus.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wow. Fuck you and your bad manners		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So ready to be home already		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm just blowin in the wind.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ready for the worst.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Well I feel sufficiently stupid.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Whatever. I'm done bothering for now ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Almost put my stuff I'm the wrong grinder, whoops! Lol		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm smirken sooooo hard. Fuck that. Laughing. This deserves a bowl it's so damn glorious.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Coughing my ass off, the "I'm Getting High" alarm is sounding		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Decided to make a coconut pastry cream tart topped with mango, pineapple, papaya, lychee, etc. for mom's birthday ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sitting here trying to figure out what this all means...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm just gonna sit here and wish you missed me too...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[He speaks in terms of centuries.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Time to get ready for work.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Made the arrangements for my moms birthday like a responsible adult.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Still got 40 minutes before the market opens so I can grab the last of what I need		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just enough time to get high ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I am in love with this baby pink lipstick I just got yesterday!! ????????????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Retail people love me. When I go into a store I know precisely what I want, exactly what I'm asking for, and I've already decided to buy it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Today is my mothers birthday. #queenleo ????#AllHailTheQueen ????????????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Time to get my ass up and back on track. But first this message from our cannabinoid receptors!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Whatever		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So glad to be home and reaching for the Bong.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm so tired, but got so much to do ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Trying to remember who I was ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck yeah new ghost adventures today!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ugh. Put my favorite lipstick through the wash. Still usable though. But really, lesson learned.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Trust my least favorite manager to fuck up my chances at catching the bus that would have had me home already		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[At least they were teaching me to serve beer and wines today :) ????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Up late. Up early. A protein rich breakfast before I smoke a bowl. #getfit		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My goals have evolved.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I don't give a fuck how tired you are, this is where anxiety can take you #insomnia #sleepplease		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Soooo sore and exhausted.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'll just be grateful I'm hereto hit this bong and that I've got this bong to hit.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm in so much fucking pain.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Can't decide if I'm gonna just hit the bing and grab on to some sleep, or grab some munching a first		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm leaning toward "Bong" #Truth		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[There's a piggy off my coast of the bed, snuffling for skritches ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[THC, then protein, then get stoned out of my mind #morningswithmcfly		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Increasing my intake. I'm tired of not being enough.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[New #GAC just in time for me to enjoy before I head to work? yes Yes YES!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ugh. Can't even right now.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It wouldn't even be a big deal if I wasn't so fucking hungry.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I can now serve beer, wines and some of our signature cocktails! ????????????????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Started at the bottom but I'm coming up like a beast.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I missed my intended early bus, so I hit the bong instead		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ughhhh my luck <<<<		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Haven't even gotten to work and I desperately need a shower and to wash my clothes already, if that says anything about my day so far...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The good thing about having luck like mine is its helped make my outlook this:		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's a bummer for the first 30 seconds, then there's not much point in anything but laughing it off and planning the next step.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nice karmic turn around though with a free bus ride ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The stench of Red Bull		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dozed on the mat for a good 15 minutes		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Living down the block from the high school means I get to listen to the marching band start fucking up bright and early. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Had my protein and got started on cleaning the kitchen. It's time for some rips before anything else though.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Reminds me of you		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I feel sick right now		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm just gonna hit the bong and forget		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Work 3 hours later than I expected. Shazam!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Damn it's cold in my store. Wish I hadn't forgotten my hoodie today -.-		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[God my head is killing me. Maybe I should eventually eat something today.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I think I put my finger on what's bothering me		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Work in 11 hours		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ugh, can't figure out why my eyes keep tearing up these past weeks.		]]></document>
</author>