<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="5def4eb3-e861-4864-a2f2-669680902007" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA["Fun is the enjoyment of pleasure"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username det fanns ett utvik med "sabrina without a stitch". acke nothing. @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username precis. "gladly the cross-eyed bear" och så heter de. med liksom barnramsetitlar.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[my first tweet hearing abdur give a talk reveals the yrvaken adopter rädsla to komma efter. https://t.co/1xHmfaqZ9H - http://t.co/T84otR565O		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username ? feedback?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[what women want on the dance floor - forskare har kul med avatarer 
http://t.co/6SZXBHhtas		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username pain chocolate!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I AM THE DOUGHBOY!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["The Unwisdom of Crowds?? Why people-powered revolutions are overrated" by @username http://t.co/Jf1xnrgatV		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nonsensical junk opinion piece on big data in the ny times http://t.co/KzRgtJjVw2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[ahoy, @username we need a statement: http://t.co/gqspe6LVvX		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username estland ftw @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Stillsuits are here! KTH+HVR  #fremen http://t.co/DdqzrXXtfj		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Commation is the first casualty of a riot. http://t.co/F5lrFLsPJo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username my brother once had some experienced conceptual modellers translate an ERD back & forth to/from txt. stayed pretty stable. @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username altho to b fair this talk I think was motivated by "here's a set of entities, let's explain them" no graph to begin w.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's really not the data, it's the *character* of the data. Describe the data, don't share it.  #ecir2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If we keep sharing data sets and training on them we cannot but land in overtraining and parameter fiddling. #ecir2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The original reason to share data was as much convenience as reproducibility. #ecir2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username true, but that's not a canned corpus, it's precisely what I like: it's a stream. @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username and results can be of the form: "on one month of Portuguese tweets we got the following ..."  @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  you are the query. @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username i'm in it too! @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username @username but is universal the thing? behaviour patterns differ acrs situs & r reflected in cross-platform logs.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[minidator, really? http://t.co/XyVX2EwA47		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Add data on your company: collect data on women software engineers https://t.co/dXb5I68DcH by @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[it's reviewing time again. my primary pro criteria: "fun & interesting","change","surprising"; con criterion the term "our system" ? paper.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username glöm inte baby elephants		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username @username it's turtles all the way down.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[ur en sorts akademiskt nigeriabrev jag just fick: "...As I am now applying for the United States Immigration (a.k.a. the Greed Card)..."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username" "the word trigger warning can in itself be a trigger warning" såg jag någon bli åthutad med häromnyssens.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[people in pursuit of happiness. "we ... identified and arrested the accused within six hours": http://t.co/ev4ZGni7EP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hotellbroschyren: "we invite you to discover rare, unexpected pleasures during your stay" *lite oroligt förväntansfull nu*		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hotellbroschyren: "...allow us to anticipate the details of your life as simple moments turn to lasting memories" hjälp DE ÄR SYNSKA!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[how far away from the office could I get in 10 minutes? http://t.co/8S8m9naYUM  ping @username - en isoskop!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Men vafan!? "@username: With the leaders of Germany, Sweden and Holland. We agreed to tackle benefits tourism. http://t.co/jWwzBjOySR"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The night America very nearly nuked itself. Scary.  http://t.co/grGlTcalbf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username you may well be right; my observation still stands: he is popular well outside his constituency. @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username my major point is to contrast fi w/ sw pol. competence and stubbornness is valued higher in fi; consensus in sw.  @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username i once compared sw cabinet w/ fi cabinet wrt formal educational level. striking difference. https://t.co/8DKRJDeRH7 @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Sorry, command-not-found has crashed! "		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Short paper on "Semantic Topology" accepted for poster presentation at #CIKM2014 !		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The world isn't less stable than ever.  

http://t.co/LkJg4L4IUk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username recorded future		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username the view from narva and hermannsborg over the border river to ivangorod. make sure to bring a historian!  @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Solid work, empiry with a clear theoretical base: RT "@username: Every state in the USA, ranked by its beer http://t.co/IKJwQ3QzPm"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Effekten av feodalism och socialism RmT "Life expectancy: EU vs US regions" http://t.co/B5ZD0sd2zq …via @username @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username yes, and we do, ever so often!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Obama: The defense of Tallinn and Riga and Vilnius is just as important as the defense of Berlin, Paris and London
http://t.co/gzL85me3hO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wrong type to apply: #<unspecified> 

#informativeerrormessage		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username the best way to make sure the headgear moves from a fashion statement to the mundane is to spell it in swedish: "bejsbollkeps".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ping @username ‘Satanic Children’s Big Book of Activities’ http://t.co/zwI63IL9Ui http://t.co/8Pugjyhhxc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Miguel Martínez from Signal talks about agile research in a high tech startup for reputation management. http://t.co/qfEOTdxHNo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[CLEF 2016 will be in Évora, Portugal - a world heritage city - on the theme "Europe meets Asia". #clef2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username filmerna om inspector tennyson.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How Swedes view Sweden at election time.  http://t.co/caW4OeAwBi		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username men också: "Space isn't remote at all. It's only an hour's drive away if your car could go straight upwards." / Fred Hoyle		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[xkcd is always xkcd http://t.co/LxXIwzcMD1 ... but CLEF has a partial answer here! 
http://t.co/Ud2qq8PeLc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Sorry, command-not-found has crashed!"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[command-not-found version: 0.2.44		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Apache CouchDB is running as process 20278, time to relax.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username puff puff!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Cecilia Malmström had threatened to resign over Juncker’s plans to exclude ISDS" http://t.co/N6ATs7DYq8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Anonabox suspended from Kickstarter? Wat?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username how many hidden levels in that classifier? WILL IT SCALE?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username oh! can you do summary tweets?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Yup, I'm the intelligent odor controller. http://t.co/3VL5LeLzyP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["while Russia is not a very legal state, it is highly legalistic" Anders Åslund tallies up Russia's reserves: http://t.co/EeeQ4wDWRx		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Kicking off #searchsolutions2014 @username holds forth on the Semantic Web. http://t.co/wy2jThKCVu		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Christopher Semturs of Google tells us about the challenges of text and context modelling #searchsolutions2014 http://t.co/noLuvh2D6E		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Contextual analysis w bandit metaphor to explore payoffs of algos: Katja Hoffmann of Microsoft #searchsolutions2014 http://t.co/u88wcnWw0t		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tom Mortimer of Flax compares Elasticsearch w/ Solr #searchsolutions2014 practitioners take note! http://t.co/eY91SuFfLO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Iadh Ounis and Craig McD from Glasgow U tell us about Terrier open src search engine #SearchSolutions2014 http://t.co/0Fg58hazZ7		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Richard Boulton of gov.uk talks about the peculiarities of implementing trustable site search #searchsolutions2014 http://t.co/OaNh08TRKm		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dominic Oldman, digital humanist of the British Museum, tells us about Joseph Conrad.  #searchsolutions2014 http://t.co/DQBdXmzbcl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Richard Ranft of the British Library tells us about crowdsourcing metadata for audio data #searchsolutions2014 http://t.co/zepmafJeQ3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Jochen Leidner of Thomson Reuters tells us about r&d in information access for 1G daily users #searchsolutions2014 http://t.co/aN2NzZlMDo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username hmm, yes. also, some routing issues: luxemburg, cyprus are large investors thru bank acct addresses. @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username ... but it did share information i had no idea of! @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[erlang the movie finds a new audience thru wired.  @username !

http://t.co/rxYGah09pv		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Gavagai's developer API is up! Two powerful tools to work with text data: 
/stories and /tonality! Try it at https://t.co/cV0d9B9Q5D !		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username TRANSPIRANTO! Mi myst most in flatans pampas!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Discovery learning...is criminally wasteful: “It’s very difficult to learn from the real world. Apples dropped from trees for centuries..."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Solstice		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Satanist group mounts holiday Snaketivity Scene" http://t.co/GzHZHCrJXz (found via Gavagai monitor http://t.co/ah4OSwClmx )		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Medelvärden döljer information 

Top tipplers: measuring national booziness - From The Economist Espresso

http://t.co/AZkyCGE6bY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Started: Sun Dec 28 10:54:43
2378817162 words processed
Finished: Mon Dec 29 09:37:07		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username jonathan livingston penguin		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I do not intend for a moment to minimise Aaronson's suffering." *immediately proceeds to relativize and trump it* http://t.co/67HPlbpvNJ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username piratstreaming istf torrent.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username hon gjorde ett utvik! "the teenage witch without a stitch"!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username four corners		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username the other day @username coined "folkölsislamolog" which should be on the list of must-have neologisms of 2015		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username wonderful! thank you!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Report by @username  - #JeSuisCharlie Movement Leveraged to Distribute DarkComet Malware https://t.co/k9sOEpKjbg		]]></document>
</author>