<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="68321c6d-6e38-4dd3-9a1a-535a25454d9b" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[It'd be stupid for me to not take advantage of that.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I got nopale breath. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Kanye's the most swaggest dude on this planet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm the most indecisive person you'll ever meet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Thinking of changing my major but don't know what too.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Cause music program at stc is wack, and I don't needa pay them to teach me when I can learn on my own		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Got an interview at Zumies tomorrow. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You know I love you like good food I'm a good dude.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tiptoeing in my chanclas		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Every time I look in the mirror I imagine the nice ass body I have the potential to have if I actually committed to the gym.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hope I do well at my interview tomorrow		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sexually frustrated		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I don't believe that I was put on this earth to be ordinary.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Any barber shops open right now?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I got the most fucked up haircut ever. I just wanna curl up in a ball and cry man.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck. This is a fucked up day.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The most fucked up part is that I'm going to have a fucked up haircut on my own birthday man!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't wish this on my worst enemy.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Bro this shit is worse than when I fucked up my own hair. Haha		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hopefully they call me back do this job at Zumies.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hopefully they call me back for this job at Zumies.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Right when I leave the mall I get a call, and guess what? I got the job!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thanks bro. I'm so happy if you were around I'd pick you up and kiss you on the lips. Extra homo. Hahaha		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[???????????? “@username: Some girl better give @username the cheeks for getting that job though.”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Getting this job made me forget about my fucked up hair, until I looked In the mirror		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Lady at the salon thought I asked for the 'lebron' style haircut or some shit cause she fucked my shit… http://t.co/Yh3fFmJoMP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I like the way you work it, no diggity. I'd like to bag it up.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username My nigga Richard 2 states away and still being my wingman aha ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You wassup girl, ain't even gotta ask it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My mom is making some bomb diggity enchiladas ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username No doubt bro. I miss your ass.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[And I miss your ass too @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You can give a women the world,  and all she'd want is to post your pics of y'all together on IG		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Belly		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Haha no for real look it up		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I don't know what it is about females. But I ain't too good at that shit.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I been listening to oldies all day bruh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I just want great sex and great company.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[As the marihuana burns we can take our turns, singing them dirty rap songs.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No sheep in my wolf pack.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Everyone is screenshotting the snapchats of my fucked up head. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Y'all just a bunch of cyber bullies		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I still want to watch the purge 2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I dont have any money that's why I haven't gone lol		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Can't nothing bring me down.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Haha you don't gotta do that. I'll come up with some moneyss		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Aww, I didn't know that. Lol alright I can't deny that. I'm down		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[lmaooo ???? “@username: Kids these days lol ???? #aysiaysi #tehuelelacola ???????? https://t.co/hWFYJGfFdL”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Lmao, this one has the proper nutrients to give you eagle powers though.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Come with me and you'll be in for a ride.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[There's been a pile of close on my bed all day ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I like the way you work it no diggity		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I was tryna sneak off to mcdonalds n my lil sis caught me n I tell her I'm going to the cemetery as a cover up but she still wanted to go ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I expected her to be scared and not wanna go, but surprisingly she did. Lol		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Had to buy her mcdonalds		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Girls are confusing		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Can't tell me nothing x Kanye West will forever be my shit		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Someone get me Kanyes Louis Vuitton collab shoes, and I'll forever be your sex slave. If you're male, we can just be homies.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Don't fuck with the angel dust		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I gotta help my mom do some shit OUTSIDE. Brb gonna go melt ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tired as fuck		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Happy Birthday! ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: I wanna purge!” ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Maybe.. If I like the purge 2 once I watch it. Lol		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I switch from twitter on my iPod to my iPhone. Pointless I know idk why		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I have my headphones in and I keep thinking I'm hearing shit.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Music doesn't help me sleep anymore. Especially listening to a song named Insomniak.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You calling me fat?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm not awake, I'm in a lake I'll swim away with you.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wanted to wake up early so I can get myself a breakfast taco but yeah I didn't see that happening		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[After party at quix's!, right infront of the Aj Walgreens on 495 and Raul longoria , 102 Maria lane sj tx		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Can't enjoy my 40 ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Come thru...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wanna do drunk nigga shit right now cause I'm a drunk nigga		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I ain't drunk enough, but just enough. If that makes any sense		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Doritos on smack right now		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm posted.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'll make it worth it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Mcdonalds coming In clutch right now		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ate my food too fast now i got the hiccups like a biyatch.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Think ima head to bed soon.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cruising through the city at night blasting music can never get old.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Oh the idea Is fun		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I love it when you give me head, I hate it when you give me headaches.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Never get your hopes up. Always expect the worse, and hope for the best		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ion ever waste time tryna spit game at girls cause I'm pretty sure i ain't saying nothing they ain't heard before		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Always kept it real		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just wait a couple months and you gon see. You'll never find nobody better than me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ain't got nothing to prove, unless I gotta prove it in court.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username That song has been stuck in my head since I first heard it. & I still be bumpin it even though I got negative Hoes. Lmao		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username It is super catchy. Haha		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Whose tryna do some late night math right now? 
Add you & me.
Subtract our clothes.
Divide your legs 
& pray to god we don't multiply.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Is the closest person to be like Huntermoore on here so he gets my follow.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I can't eat hot n spicys without buffalo sauce.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tables turn bridges burn you live and learn.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Beyoncé ain't the best, and jay z doesn't represent the entire male population.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Attracted to what's in your attic (mind) can we mind fuck.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Had to put that annotation for those of you who don't understand		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I just got hired there too. Lol		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The bitch I'm smashing into fashion but I know the devil wear a leopard coat.		]]></document>
</author>