<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="68b27ee9-bf56-45db-be9a-2e0970d2b6b8" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username grandes coaches http://t.co/DCxQ7OzAQf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username way to GO! Congrats		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username: I love how you write! I wish I could have half of your talent to express my feelings in writing.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Remembre it only takes ONE negative comment to kill a dream". Think about that when someone share it with you.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Can You Really Improve Your Emotional Intelligence? http://t.co/gsn1YBY7O1”Coaching works!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username si muchas grax		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Kindness is the language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see" Mark Twain		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Logic will get you from A to B. Imagination will take you everywhere" Albert Einstein		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Smart answer		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["The artist is nothing without the gift, but the gift is nothing without work" Emile Zola		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Y sigo con mi country music, sugarland it happens...sugarland - it happens (live at cma fest 2009) http://t.co/CbGmh0Fa3o		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A jugar solitario antes de decidir “@username:Why You Might Make a Better Decision After a Quick Game of Solitaire http://t.co/aZlbS5rovK”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If you could accomplish only One thing right now, what would that be? Si sólo pudieras realizar una cosa en este momento que sería? #goals		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Beauty isn't in the mirror, It's in the light of your heart! #quote		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Knowing what you want is the first step toward getting it!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username spend time with my family and friends its my dopamine		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: "Happiness is not something ready made. It comes from your own actions." 
~Dalai Lama”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username muchas gracias Charly y mucho gusto Larry		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: 70% of women ask questions in which they already know the answer to. This is why it's best to simply tell her the truth.”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: RT @username: There will be many chapters in your life. Don't get lost in the one you're in now. ~		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Find the sweetness in your own heart, 
then you may find the sweetness in every heart. #rumi” me encanto!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username: ‘We want coaching,’ say high-fliers - http://t.co/0dogaoAg9p http://t.co/U843BVtwM7		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Music is escape for #Leo from the bullshit in life.”correcto!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username: “Executives and HR managers know coaching is the most potent tool for inducing lasting personal change.” (Ivy Business Journal)”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: You can’t escape the responsibility of tomorrow by evading it today. -Abraham Lincoln”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username for me yes!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Leaders a don't create followers, they create more leaders" Tom Peters		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[2014, new begginings, new experiences= Life is fun!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: #Leos choose their company based on morals and personality. Keep it classy or keep it moving.”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Your attitude is an expression of your values, beliefs and expectations." Muy cierto		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: "Among Fortune 500 CEOs, only six are black, eight are Asian, and eight are Hispanic." http://t.co/zxd7WBRty1” muy lamentable!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Don't choose the better person, choose the person who makes you better.” True!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username mi Charly usted proponga fecha!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username correct!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Our intention creates our reality. ~Wayne Dyer”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Should you take that international assignment? Here's how to decide http://t.co/E06HgxzyPR”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username count on it		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“With good friends, you can always find a way to laugh even in the darkest situations.” YehudaBerg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: A 4-year-old asks an average of 437 questions a day” con razón término tan cansada!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sunday the perfect Day to... http://t.co/g2BDSwZwCs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: "When someone else's happiness is your happiness, that's love."”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Mi frase hoy a meditar... http://t.co/gBWKa553fq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Hear that? Vegas is calling your name. Book now and save up to 20% off your stay. https://t.co/e38RSNeeIv”@username ojo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: "Generosity is giving more than you can, and pride is taking less than you need." - Kahlil Gibran”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: “Success is a personal standard, reaching for the highest that is in us, becoming all that we can be.” – Zig Ziglar”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username woooow a buscar hacer esos viajes!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Appreciate those who love you. Help those who need you. Forgive those who hurt you. Forget those who leave you.”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[What a wonderful World...hermosas imágenes, feliz domingo! http://t.co/FX9dNYDHzw		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Music is what feelings sounds like... Today for me sounds like magic! Rosana - Magia (Jesús Navarro de Reik)http://t.co/92qZcJ7mdn		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Words are the most powerful tool of leadership.”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: "You gotta put something in to life before you expect to get anything out."- Zig Ziglar”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: #Sharapova battles to save BPs & draw even 2-2 vs #Halep in the 3rd set. Duration:2h41min. Que buen partido vamos simonaaa		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Nine times an RG champion! What a record, @username! #RG14 http://t.co/5nDoeafZTt” yes!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username yeahhhh!!! Gracias		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Your imagination is your preview of life's coming attractions. — Albert Einstein” seraaaaa?! Qué divertido :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Take the wheel. http://t.co/0zaVp6QvBN”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["@username: Powerful Question: http://t.co/TGYH9PK1QI"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Try it... http://t.co/zR7xZnCV5Y”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: "Knowledge is having the right answer. Intelligence is asking the right question." http://t.co/foy24bFHL5”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["@username: "Look at it this way: what you do today is the most important, because you're exchanging a day of your life for it.""		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Lack of confidence isn't what keeps women from applying to jobs http://t.co/ZsOydb2NcD http://t.co/csoPpmCZEt” sad		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thanks Iya, where can I find that book? I just don't get it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username great! as soon as I finish that book I get back to you ;)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username muy lindo Fer! Kids always give us lessons :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username with what book do you recomend to start?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thanks		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Love it! http://t.co/ctNVj2nykG		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: “Laughter is timeless. Imagination has no age. And dreams are forever” - Walt Disney Company.”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username noooo hum even that enjoy!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Grandes coaches @username @username http://t.co/hmE2Js2woO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: High #EQ leaders create a safe, inspiring environment for every person, every day. ~Chris Edmonds”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: Don’t give up. No matter how tough things gets, you always want to be able to say that you gave it all you’ve got.”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: This woman’s story will show the true horrors of anorexia http://t.co/dL8UNwOlVQ http://t.co/7ma3F0iuFX” woooow pobre mujer		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Good morning! http://t.co/rVj7AxMhp3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: You got to feel it! http://t.co/biUILQWvcv” muy cierto !		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: The rules for being amazing http://t.co/aRjF5JLbL3”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: http://t.co/NG3QbFS3YI”woooow que cierto!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: A goal without a plan is just a wish. http://t.co/5kV3E5TYa2”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Enjoy the most wonderful time of the year!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Love, service, freedom... http://t.co/mz6dYEGPuB		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: We should be able to look into each other’s eyes and see the spark of God that exists.”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: People who prefer spicy foods tend to be risk-takers.”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username where can I find them?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“@username: RT@username "Goals are the links in the chain that connect activity to accomplishment." Tom Ziglar http://t.co/JYyZqBq7t2”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Lucky to be alive! Feliz martes :)		]]></document>
</author>