<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="6c5201d6-b53a-4638-a299-02aa2f2ce373" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[@username hipster! :-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username sorry to disappoint you, LREC is a two-yearly conference #LREC2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Is there an #LREC2014 participant list?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Where do we apply for other conference funding? “@username: #LREC2014 : EC will support our community... more euros ?”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Did not notice any of the promised brevity in ELRA talk. We need coffee! #LREC2014 #coffeebreakplease #overtime		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#LREC2014 tip: there's a larger coffee area downstairs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Empty room 15 minutes before keynote speech #LREC2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[2 min and 12 slides to go #o20 #LREC2014 http://t.co/EgHiPZcSZl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Like the #LREC2014 moodmap but suggest putting general tag in a separate table for more detail for the others http://t.co/6UdcCoipF7		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Great update ! Thanks for responding		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username nice talk! I’ll try to come and talk to you later		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Is @username still at #LREC2014 ? Would like to say hello		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How disappointing that this isn't for us #LREC2014 http://t.co/HkdO7VGTPM		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just presented CSI corpus for stylometry, author profiling, sentiment & deception detection #o29 #LREC2014 http://t.co/37prsNAi5B Enjoy!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Some commercial sentiment analysers under baseline for some corpora. Ouch! #o29 #LREC2014 http://t.co/4q7hBfq1TE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Microphone people should be instructed to run to people with questions. They're álways late strolling over there! #LREC2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm guessing the co-authors did not proofread these slides #lrec2014 #yesno http://t.co/oCnoqOWCZ0		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Live English to French automatic speech translation of talk by Alex Waibel  #LREC2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Live English to French automatic speech translation of talk by Alex Waibel  #LREC2014 http://t.co/dgaUHa0cFU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username i see only 3 tweets with lrec and o1 hashtags. Seems like sth went wrong, lots of irrelevant tweets w only #o1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Really liked #LREC2014, though the lack of twitter interaction saddened me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username there was quite some action, but interaction less so imo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username exactly what I meant, but I’ve experienced #ICWSM13 which raises expectations :-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username hey June, don't make it bad. Take a sad song and make it better #nananananana		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Only if there's an international airport		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username going to #tedxghent tomorrow? I'd come and say hello :-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username So, where are you headed?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Are you changing jobs as well? Thought you had a postdoc?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Great to meet @username at #TEDxGhent today. Until we meet again, my friend! http://t.co/H7rCKzL6YK		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Life’s great, thanks! TedxGhent was worth attending. Saw some really cool talks, want to share this video  https://t.co/v7TNOUzjwR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username i've registered for @username 's klout party in Antwerp in july. Maybe there?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is my 1111th tweet. Glad I did something useful with it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to an interesting  #DHBenelux conference! Now up: keynote by @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Dkh4LpgLnq -> cool crowdsourced map (and routeplanner!) of Roman Empire by @username at #dhbenelux		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Imagine a virtual choir by crowdsourcing of youtube videos #DHBenelux http://t.co/ZnhVWMcHQK		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Virtual art by #crowdsourcing see Eric Whitacre, eg http://t.co/jErBDh1lDm #dhbenelux		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Some really great research on music being presented at the #DHBenelux poster session		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username only if we consider both to be a cultural issue where women are less technologically inclined #dhbenelux		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username Will do! Great suggestions, @username. Thanks!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thanks! Glad you enjoyed it :-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Haha, no worries. Walter (my supervisor) will be delighted to hear that people find him to be looking so young ;-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Pics or it didn't happen		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Oh my god. No Facebook! #thehorrorthehorror		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Maybe check if the air starts drooling if you ring a bell, then it's already conditioned		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[An Ugly Fruit That Inspired a Beautiful Idea. http://t.co/X4YnLb5dSn via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Nice review! Very welcome in Antwerp for the 2015 edition ;-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Finally some emotion on their faces! RT @username: Royal enthusiasm, we love it! #BelRus #WorldCup2014 #monarchy http://t.co/g5jdUJZdCA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is no formula! RT @username: Ever wonder how Klout measures influence? Here’s the formula! #SMInfluencers http://t.co/toPWlQwcD1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username Africa is not a country		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username I smell a secret friend-making tactic :-D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Courtois was man of the match! #korbel #zkobel @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm cheering for @username. Though I'm already Belgian, I Belgiumized my name to Boudewijn Van den Broeck at belgiumizeme.be #worldcup		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Because of course		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username didn't you do that the week before #dh2015 ?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Say hi to my South African friend Wikus Pienaar at @username for me, will you? :-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I don’t have a clue :-P Sorry! I didn’t know @username was so big you wouldn’t meet everyone.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username You heard them, Merisa. You have to meet :-D By the way, Have fun!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why everyone should learn it a little: 10 places where anyone can learn to code http://t.co/3rMM0aZt2i		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Studying a language is like drinking from a mental fountain of youth." http://t.co/64imRJzHGq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Up next: Harry Potter strippoker. "I found the golden snatch - I mean, snitch"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How to encourage girls to choose IT or learn programming  https://t.co/I0GFEnfQ45 Congrats to @username and Jane!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username It's actually the opposite of the fightclub rules:
1) You DO talk about the conference
2) You DO talk about the conference		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username And will the programme be available before that deadline? Would be handy		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thanks for concern. Terrible news indeed, but no personal losses.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Great! Looking forward to it !		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I don't get it. Why don't you like the name of this Dutch café/restaurant?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Probably selection is so strict that you're not in as soon as there is doubt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Dutch: "Hallo, Wereld"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username ben er! #team610 for the win :-D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username and far more clean and safe, says every sane person :-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username i think you should come to the office more often! :-) when is that cellar ready btw? :-D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username quick question: can I save a #pattern datasheet without the quotation marks around every value?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username wanted to make the file uniform w others, no worries, have decided to leave it be ;-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username also really looking forward to it!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Right now, my Kardashian-index is 9.1 (182/20). Scientists, check yours! (twitter followers / citations) http://t.co/hUqAGmJIRA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Or, people will have to start citing me more. :-)  No, I think the K-index can only be used for postdocs and professors.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username The best time to actually make the booking, or the best time for which you should book?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Oh :-( I only read the @username article, not the paper		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Not sure whether the amount of interaction in DH is always reflected in nr of followers.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username How can one request support for an academic event from Elsevier? (linguistics)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username How can one request support for an academic event from John Benjamins? (linguistics)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Trying to contact #Nuance marketing office for academic event sponsorship (comput. linguistics) can you refer me? Thanks!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username oh, dat was retorisch, sorry #LT		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Probably both. Visibility is always important and I hear there are also still a couple of #Nuance job openings in our region		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Region is Belgium/Netherlands. Info from Peter Dirix (Mngr Linguistic Engineering @username Nuance), regular attendee of event. #LT		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google Scholar just changed the lay-out of the author profiles. Check mine for a quick sample: http://t.co/plCKMDFe5U		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hi Peter, could you direct me to recruitment marketing then? Thanks again!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username MT @username: wout: a guy who is very athletic, bit of a geek and loves... http://t.co/iNUIahqFHz http://t.co/elgKOVccGD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username shartie got low, low, low, ...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Is there an attendee list available?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thanks!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Presentation language can be weird. "We decided to perform evaluation." Well, duh! #COLING2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Looking forward to your defense ;-) who's in the jury?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Same here! Right now mostly tired though. At the airport before 5am.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username A folded giraffe? The boat was not thát big, you know.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My followers live in Belgium (64%), Netherlands(9%)... Get your free map too: http://t.co/0auCB0LrwR http://t.co/FgzmWSDsoI		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username clint.be		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thanks, already knew it. As far as I understand uses doc/par id for word repr, no real doc repr		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[For every tweet with #apearforanapple Samsung will hand out a pear in Brussels. Still love Apple products though :-)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[.@username It's always cold and windy in this building. Can the AC be turned off or warmer?		]]></document>
</author>