<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="7418df48-598b-49df-9ccb-be12715c21ea" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[Center of Attention: How Facebook Users Allocate Attention across Friends - Lars Backstrom, Eytan Bakshy,... http://t.co/JryhbZdP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Stroke Victims Learn Steps To Recovery Using Wii Game @username http://t.co/cn5SSqhk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Weight Watchers Creates Virtual Support Network To Promote Healthy Living @username http://t.co/SrVY2FVv		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nike Builds Online Motivational Community Through Twitter @username - Nike is engaging its fans to build a... http://t.co/FO2XoZAO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Need A Kidney? Check Facebook via @username http://t.co/6FYRiG6u		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Kids Think Technology is Fundamentally Human - › These kids, the ‘digital natives,” are raised with modern... http://t.co/X4P3MrSk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[visualization with d3 (By Mike Dewar) via Vimeo http://t.co/VZIMMkc8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[women more likely to buy consumer electronics than men http://t.co/GnqH0Bp4		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A Wristwatch That Tracks Your Heartbeats And Analyzes The Data @username - A 3D accelerometer [that] measures... http://t.co/hnRjtqN7		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[5 Ways That Android Is Trying To Break The Mobile UI Paradigm - via Co.Design http://t.co/IoxPwOma		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[[Infographic] Pasta, Not Bacon, Makes You Fat. via codesign http://t.co/0zhz51Vn		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Video: (via The Rise of the e-Patient) http://t.co/9nMxYtwT		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Luxury Hospitals Compete For Wealthy Patients @username - The New York Times reports that V.I.P. rooms at the... http://t.co/t5acCZ7x		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Video: Kinshasa One Two Project ‘Can Creativity Be Agile?’ (via @username) http://t.co/Pk8uMQ5s		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: Pharmacy’s New Branding Cures The Design Blahs (via Co.Design: business innovation design) http://t.co/ZdEw4dm3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Planned Parenthood Patient Care services breakdown: http://t.co/OWNKeBvI		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[5 planes of ux http://t.co/kqjOR7eF		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[the ux wheel http://t.co/6LBxpcT7		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: The Psychology of Color (via Cool Infographics) http://t.co/CUFLgLTs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: The N.F.L. Players Mentioned Most on “SportsCenter” (via http://t.co/JrKE6HR5) innovative use of figures! http://t.co/LCA2KFjj		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Most health solutions aren’t medical, they’re social. http://t.co/mgZGZCHe		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Use Your Smartphone to Refill Your Prescriptions at CVS http://t.co/jKBzEGAn		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[First drafts come from the heart. Second drafts come from the head. - Dr. Rachna Jain		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Video: (via Designing For CX (The UX of Social Media)) http://t.co/DGRiWgVU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[15 Unconventional Jobs For a Computer Science Major http://tumblr.com/xyb13hd1ut		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: Four Ways to Mix Fonts (via Ask H&FJ) http://t.co/AtWcbk99		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[XRDS: Smarter Cities: Making societies smarter - Peter J. McNerney and Ning Zhang. 2011. Smarter Cities:... http://t.co/eauzm8L5		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Usability testing EHRs - Art Swanson and Scott Lind. 2011. Usability testing EHRs: examples from the front... http://t.co/I8R0MMK2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Video: Creating a Culture of UX (via Whitney Hess) http://t.co/4G1kE9Xg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Asthma disproportionately affects low-income populations / UCLA Newsroom http://tumblr.com/xyb13ledvu		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: A house designed like a web application (via David Galbraith’s Blog) Yes, he gets it! — “A user’s... http://t.co/IHuCgzdl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Technology As A Material - To make art with technology, one does not use it as a tool; one must understand... http://t.co/mxZuonre		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Eytan Bakshy's study of 250 mill Facebook users supports Granovetter's theory on the strength of weak ties http://t.co/aAjNyHVO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: Where Does Product Management Belong in the Organization? (via Pragmatic Marketing) “As companies... http://t.co/TgAZoBcx		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Video: Mobile, Social, Games, Texts…and Health | Pew Research Center’s Internet & American Life Project http://tumblr.com/xyb13sbxpz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Smith said that though Pew doesn’t know why people in small towns are so much less likely to use..." http://tumblr.com/xyb13t3s78		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How Target Figured Out A Teen Girl Was Pregnant Before Her Father Did - Forbes - › [Pole] ran test after... http://t.co/zttvv10r		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[responsive wireframing examples http://t.co/JBrirP1h		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: The life of an Internet Meme http://t.co/ReujejqV		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[[Chart] parkinson's law... "work always expands to fill time available" http://t.co/dib8GZWS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[[Photo] tools #evolution http://t.co/Qarh77TH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Global Publics Embrace Social Networking via Pew Research Center's Internet & American Life Project -... http://tumblr.com/xyb13y6tuk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Women Underestimate Their Performance on the Job - The Juggle - WSJ http://tumblr.com/xyb13yp4ya		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HCI student robbed, uses iPhone to catch culprits | Human-Computer Interaction Institute http://tumblr.com/xyb13z6jck		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Newlywed Man to Divorce Wife he claims faked leukemia to score free dress and honeymoon - newsweek: http://tumblr.com/xyb13zpsuc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Design isn’t about making things look pretty, it’s about making things functional in an aesthetic way." http://tumblr.com/xyb140ee3d		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo:  http://t.co/JbX4kCeR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Happiness is not a destination - bobulate: http://t.co/XFxugwsK		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: (via A Day in the Life of the Internet [INFOGRAPHIC]) http://t.co/VUKngOqf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Quote: "Growth and comfort do not coexist." Virginia Rometty http://t.co/zTQZ93Bp		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[8 Job-Getting Tips from a Guy Who's Hired 500 People in the Past 5 Years via Wise Bread http://tumblr.com/xyb1470vqt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[5 Predictions for Online Data In 2011 - 1. “Data scientist” Is the New Community Manager 2. Data Management... http://tumblr.com/xyb147il1q		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: Facebook Upgrades Photos: Look Out, Flickr http://tumblr.com/xyb1483rrc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: The Startup Curve (via swissmiss) http://t.co/stQbrJMM		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: The Methodology Translator (via PHD Comics) http://t.co/UUL8ufy7		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: Everyone Uses E-mail, But Blogging Is On the Decline [STUDY] http://tumblr.com/xyb149izzk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: What Would Facebook and Twitter Sneakers Look Like? [PICS] http://tumblr.com/xyb14a9jbv		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: 10 Creative Uses of the New Facebook Profile [PICS] http://tumblr.com/xyb14b1t62		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Maternal leave now possible with NSF grants - Thank you, Mrs. Obama! Supporting work-life balance for our... http://t.co/iY8LmwCN		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[5 Important Tips for Better Eye Health in a Digital World - Customize your environment Think about lighting... http://tumblr.com/xyb14bu9rf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["WHY WRITING A DISSERTATION IS HARDER THAN HAVING A BABY 1. Three months before your due date, your..." http://t.co/jxTdTT7B		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username things are going well!! almost done with first draft!! how's life going for you?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Link: searching for best hotel prices using predictive algorithms http://t.co/miXi6Gy9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username wow, congrats on the position!! =)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[[Infographic] The History of Apple Products http://t.co/KJUNrgR2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: The Wealth Divide in Internet Usage [STATS] http://tumblr.com/xyb14for44		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Watchie GPS watch empowers Alzheimer's and Dementia patients http://t.co/SKGAGep3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Intel Infographic Generator App http://t.co/21RQxtCy		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[NoRedInk App - automating grading process for english teachers http://t.co/weFyVqMA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How Online Retailers Can Leverage Facebook's Open Graph http://tumblr.com/xyb14gpsbo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Video: Jer Thorp: Make data more human (via Video on http://t.co/kcFKejBL) http://t.co/8je8M8v1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How Consumers Are Using Smartphones in Stores [STUDY] - Other findings: 52% used their smartphones to find a... http://tumblr.com/xyb14heien		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[6 Ways to Score a Job Through Twitter - Tweet like an industry expert Use twitter hashtags Connect with... http://tumblr.com/xyb14i4ycl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: Holiday Shopping Online - Social Media Graphics http://tumblr.com/xyb14j7t94		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: The Santa Brand Book – Marketing Guidelines From The North Pole http://tumblr.com/xyb14jr9ld		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I just got a $5 credit for movies and TV shows @username. Click http://amzn.to/hh8gTP to get yours. #get5		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: Cool Infographics - Blog - Christmas in the World 2010 http://tumblr.com/xyb14k6xhc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: jerrylieveld: disciplines of design http://t.co/JknDTMy2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: (via A Lot of Android Phones and Condoms Share the Same Name) http://t.co/bJJRaGHJ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: 5 Innovative Technologies Changing Health Care [VIDEOS] http://tumblr.com/xyb14nd3vg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: Visualizing Bloodtests http://tumblr.com/xyb14noxpe		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Shrinking Female IT Workforce - Women in mid-management are leaving IT at an alarming rate. The tough... http://tumblr.com/xyb14ogk6w		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: › Recognizing that females have risen to 44% of the American football fan population, the NFL opened... http://tumblr.com/xyb14ovfi8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sports and Social Media: Why the Best Is Yet to Come - Fans have proven time and again that they want to... http://tumblr.com/xyb14pa0qm		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[New Studies Show That Your Spending Habits Say a Lot About How Cool You Are - › according to a new study,... http://t.co/bKubGid9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Startup HealthRally hopes social is the secret ingredient for wellness - › [HealthRally], a new San... http://t.co/nb7tIgRY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why a Woman's Razor Costs More Than a Man's, and Other Fun Facts - The New York Times confirms that gender... http://t.co/QsvYYUkT		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[75+ Ways to Do Good With Social Media http://tumblr.com/xyb14posy6		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: What the jobs data tells us: Trends in health care hiring http://t.co/K4mXdlKi		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Love Your Users - › In November 2009, a pharmacist working for the Department of Veterans Affairs was... http://tumblr.com/xyb14q3z8h		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Video: Name: DailyFeats Big Idea: DailyFeats offers a way for people to get motivated to achieve their... http://t.co/uqmKC784		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: ilovecharts: http://t.co/aLhphKsu		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: Behind the Scenes of the World’s First Live-Tweeted Open-Heart Surgery (via Mashable) Doctors at... http://t.co/iBjxXUUP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Big Squeeze - Pressed for higher productivity, yet pinched by flat wages, many IT workers are ready to... http://tumblr.com/xyb14qkly5		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Video: Health I.T.- Advancing Care, Empowering Patients (via Discovery CME) Discovery Channel presents an... http://t.co/3knev6IF		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: How a Niche Shopping Site Plans to Transform Local Economies (via hellodoctorkitty) http://tumblr.com/xyb14vflzi		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fashion Line Gets an Interactive Twist with Microsoft Tags - › Shoppers can use the Microsoft Tag Reader app... http://tumblr.com/xyb14vwr7i		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: Facebook status updates: young people are self-centered and old ramble http://tumblr.com/xyb14wfyhq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Simplified Model via http://t.co/a7wElc2I http://t.co/gdu4ayyC		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Extended Model via http://t.co/a7wElc2I http://t.co/0TYtEJFf		]]></document>
</author>