<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="7b2bdc7a-cfee-4b1d-acfb-7ae140bb4a38" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[Looking for my paralel line.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[AND EVEN IF THEY TRYYYYYYYYY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[THEY'LL NEVER TAKE MY BODY FROM YOUR SIDEEE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wish I was not how I am.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username not in my casa :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Stop pretending life doesn't terrify you".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Don't grow up... IT'S A TRAP!"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I might not be the same, but that's not important".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["And I can't change, even if I try".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["It’s impossible to find someone who will never hurt you, so go for the one who’s always worth all the pain".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[CUANDO TE MIRO Y NO ME MIRAS...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Prove they're wrong.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[DÓNDE TENGO METIDA LA CABEZAAAAAAAAAAAAA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Wise men talk because they have something to say. Fools talk because they have to say something."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[We keep lying ourselves so we can feel alive.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username mis apuntes son muy top.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Kingdom of ice-olation.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I want it back.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck logic.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Im back, bitches. http://t.co/ItXXCCTA6g		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[BBK Live Festival, I'm on my way!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Still looking for the light that wakes me up.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["A boy so pretty with an ugly heart".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“Pato, I am this close to falling in love with you, but im not gonna do that to myself if you’re not ready. And I dont think you’re ready.”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[NOCHE DE FLEXOOOOOO!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I want her back so bad... that I leave the door unlocked. I leave the lights on".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pure randomness.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I have the feeling of living, but do I really live?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Brand flaming  JAJIJOJIIJAOJOADJAODAJO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["If you give up too soon, you'll never know that you'll be missing."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[AYAYAYAAYYAYAY VOY A VER EL NUEVO CAP DE JDTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTT #emosion #jartatac #mimuero		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Life is a beautiful sport".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["The inevitable tradeoff between what is physically realistic and what is mathematically possible".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Sometimes all you need is someone who cares".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You are like the top of a mountain. The highest risk, but the highest reward.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When everything arounds me goes wrong, it is maybe because im what's wrong.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Sometimes people are beautiful. Not in looks. Not in what they say. Just in what they are".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["You know that place between sleep and awake... the place where you can still remember dreaming? That's where I'll always love you...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[... That's where I'll always be waiting." Peter Pan. J.M. Barrie.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is a nice day to be a birthday.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Night's still young.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I'm a little too young with not enough time".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Good morning, darling.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["You and me at the edge of the world".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Will this be the 1000? http://t.co/wO3NoL9ZHS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["And when the stars come out, I wanna be with you".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Guiri, esa worldwide known palabra.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When you don't get a joke... And you look for someone who doesn't get it either.. But you keep laughing. https://t.co/4fybjKevIA JAJAJAJAJA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[JAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJJJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAAJAJAJJA TAN PUTO CIERTOOOOOOOOOOOO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Fuck what they think".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Am I the bear or the honey?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Someday it will happen".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the most obvious things are the most difficult to be said.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Those pieces of you that you had to leave behind.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You Ludus while I Ágape		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Spotlight Effect		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username er what?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Your mind tells you what's smart, and your heart tells you what you are going to do anyways."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing over and over again and expecting the results to change".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["You have to be the change you want to see in the world."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["At the gym i'm like a ninja. You'll never see me there".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["This room is hot, but we could make it hotter with your help".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Gente con gatos BASTA YA DE MANDAR FOTOS POR WHATSAPP CON ESOS SERES TAN ACHUCHABLES. Besis.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Sometimes tears are a sign of unspoken happiness and a smile is a sign of silent pain".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["When everyone else is more comfortable remaining voiceless, rather than fighting for humans that have had their rights stolen".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I might not be the same, but that’s not important". http://t.co/2mkrEnGlDd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[As if nothing had happened, I suppose.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I cant stand to hear the silence of a busy train, where no one wants to talk for the fear of looking insane".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username http://t.co/gclRczY3ZK's today design is LoL related! http://t.co/ew8unu3iLn Cute poros for everyone!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pues Finlandia se lleva muchos thumbs up.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["In every breath I take I'm breathing you".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Experience is what you get, when you dont get what you wanted".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["And we'll pretend that the world will never end".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[American Authors definitivamente molan demasiado.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No books, no fucking.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I knew she was trouble from the first case".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[On fire. http://t.co/Fhx3sjNNtY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Moving everydayyy going further on! http://t.co/bn6B7V5GDd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["The nights are long but the stars are brighter" http://t.co/jOh3vqvm0Q		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Me hacen bowling. #Concepto		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["We can't keep running from who we are".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Stuck on you.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["And those who were seen dancing were thought to be insane by those who could not hear the music". Friedrich Nietzsche		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hold me closer, hold me tighter.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username think so pero confírmalo mejor		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Surreal. #Concepto @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Parents definition of a "Mess"???? https://t.co/pt0yMPSiNo EN SERIO ES QUE NO PUEDO CON ESTE HOMBRE JAJAJAJJAAJJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJJAJAJAJAJAJAAJAJ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Follow the path. You'll arrive somewhere. http://t.co/4kDGl3gldg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Al fin podré twittear cosas muy ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Me hacen bowling por Twitter y pues yo yoro.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#RetoDeTronos Día 1: Jon Snow. http://t.co/YMyqGPo6yR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username JAJAJAJAJAJAJAJJAJAJAJAJAJAJJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJJAJAJAJAJA MUEROOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When liking lasts so long, it starts to mean something different.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username chungo handshake JAJAJAJAJAJ matásme, carol		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username @username @username es que bitchy owner solo hay una mai lof ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Hope. It is the only thing stronger than fear."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["then we have the other ignorant assholes who call girls “sluts” “slags” “bitches” “whores” “thots” for being confident with what they wear"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[WE'LL BE COMING BACK FOR YOU ONE DAY!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username #CosasJugosas JJAJAJAJ basta de bowling joaco basta		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["You love me. Real or not real?" I tell him, "Real." #HG		]]></document>
</author>