<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="89fab4e9-24f0-4a97-8e10-ca357cc7865c" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[World Cup to kick-off with brain-wave bionics http://t.co/DPzHrEoIYz "All these tools are not a cure"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wow fantastica videolezione! di @username > Tetris has also been involved in some important psychological research http://t.co/Jhr7H1uBMS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Stamina Foundation stem cell trial first stopped in Italy & then reinstated by judge.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Maybe if we had chosen this treatment [w mesenchymal cells]much earlier the outcome would have been different http://t.co/KuwqWrw0Ho #badsci		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["it won’t be too long before a woman drives in an F1 Grand Prix". Conversation w/ @username - Esquire http://t.co/ByPSiTnjfS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[appena pubblicato!> Schizophrenia: One approach is to consider the possibility of demonic possession http://t.co/3lBERnWu23 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[utile >"it would be useful for medical professions to work together w/ faith healers to define better treatment pathways for schizophrenia"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Brenda Milner receives Dan David Prize > Mind and Memory: Biological and Digital, Part I: http://t.co/s7X9I5Y61S		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username and what about neuropsychological testing (attention, executive functions, ...), is it usually performed?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thank You Doc!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pinchas Zuckerman > Bruch - Violin Concerto No. 1 in G minor - I. Vorspiel: Allegro moderato http://t.co/YLnQDd0ktz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Writing In The 21st Century, @username http://t.co/kmELI0Htwr @username "having an editor is a really good thing", "focus should be on ideas"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Intelligent (wild) Crows Flunk Causality Test (But Babies Pass) by @username   http://t.co/llxnJfTGio		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pop pop pop > World cup: Why mirror neurons play a part in jubilation http://t.co/slSuIuVz42 >Inaccurate apology. From Parma to Vienna w/ ?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Today > One giant leap for science, one small step for disability... a winning race for advertising http://t.co/BThl5SDrNV #exoskeleton		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to explain this idea is to contrast it, for example, with advertising. Richard Feynman http://t.co/YOFEb4XIvD #exoskeleton		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Recession 'led to 10,000 suicides' http://t.co/rNWQV7czHA "it reminds us how important is to take preventative action"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[1881, scacchi="unsocial game" > That time when people thought playing chess would make you violent http://t.co/MrngdLDox9 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Favoloso! > The History of the Typewriter:  Michael Winslow Performs the Sounds of 32 Typewriters (1898-1983) http://t.co/UnuVw2psPR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's time for a shower... #Icastica2014 Michal Trpak http://t.co/KkZviq4QgI		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Una leggenda vivente / She is the Violin > Ida Haendel M Bruch, Violin Concerto 1 Op. 26 http://t.co/SmrmaS84H0		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This article by Feinstein (1997) Psychosurgery & the child prodigy  http://t.co/rNdsUDzTiZ inspired my new post (ita) http://t.co/r3JV1jAg2Q		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Josef Hassid the celebrated violin virtuoso who died from an infection following prefrontal leucotomy at Longrove https://t.co/QAXtsVM5nj...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ida Hendel shared w/ Josef Hassid the first steps of their career,from Poland to London. She's 85, still play violin https://t.co/0hx88ztHVW		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Some events are perceived as so unique that past history does not seem relevant to the evaluation of their likelihood<Availability heuristic		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Availability heuristic, Tversky and Kahneman 1973 http://t.co/udOSIKDnR6		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sarah Macdonald investigates the sinister disappearance of 500 Albanian 'street children from a Greek State orphanage http://t.co/lDnoYothOI		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[But there is one 16th-century village in southern Italy where migrants can expect a warm welcome > #Riace < http://t.co/lUlTT1mFJg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Spiders & Music: they rely on the vibration of the silk in their web for sensory information http://t.co/aO2SRYpSGm via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Poverty: If I’m short on money, I can’t stop thinking about today’s expenses-never mind those in the future http://t.co/djPk25C7RQ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[First walk in #Icastica2014= to know contemporary art and to recognize the medieval Arezzo https://t.co/UfqFifRWZ6		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Irresistibile > Ida Haendel plays informally Part 1 (2009, at 80 yo) http://t.co/iRwJAWqXkS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Gun violence and mental illness: Study addresses perception vs. reality http://t.co/EkGiqKiEQG > media attention make the difference		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Put down the smart drugs – cognitive enhancement is ethically risky business http://t.co/s3Md1nRYwf ethics and responsible enhancement		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[NO News. Qualche informazione seria su Schumacher > "@username: Good news? http://t.co/PpLxe8USzZ" "cynical use of language"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Elena Cattaneo & Gilberto Corbellini su Nature > Stem cells: taking a stand against pseudoscience http://t.co/HsR2iuogDL #Stamina		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Your least favorite virtue,or nominee for the most overrated one? Faith.Closely followed-in view of the overall shortage of time-by patience		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Science of Laughter with @username  http://t.co/xU3jLR92ro via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Visual Illusions & tricks < wow > OK Go - The Writing's On the Wall - Official Video: http://t.co/3CVHuhI4GL via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[lesson learned> Regulation: Sell help not hope http://t.co/v44fvHN6VZ Taking a stand against pseudoscience http://t.co/ZHNpcgoLk3 #StemCells		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username +Paolo Bianco & Douglas Sipp http://t.co/PCs4ypl7na lesson learned after the dark:Stamina Foundation & institutional mistakes		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Temporal dynamics of hippocampal neurogenesis [dentate gyrus] during chronic neurodegeneration #OA from @username http://t.co/fElFu78BcL		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Children w/ focal epilepsy & L-hemisphere seizures are at increased risk of language impairment #OA http://t.co/pcgdibU1Lx via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Most People Think Alzheimer's Is a Normal Part of Aging  http://t.co/P6kgL0uJWQ "Aging is not a disease" Professor Marco Trabucchi,20 ys ago		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Freud We Wish For http://t.co/vzU5lW8IAt interesting book review of Adam Phillips' Becoming Freud		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username nearby the historical hospital of Longrove... ;-) @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[ISIL video shows children in arms http://t.co/kgPOkU6UQ6 #Iraq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Great Divide: Gaming the Poor http://t.co/d6uzDTX6CT US:Most harmful effects of Casino gambling in lower socioeconomic& minority groups		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Constructors' Championship: 3. Ferrari 98 <> 4. Force India 87 #byebye		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Un robot per la nonna > Changing Batteries - The Saddest Story 3D Animation: http://t.co/OohEIwxqys a robot companion for elderly people		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Hit songs help memory research http://t.co/fVOAbjzoPX Get involved here > http://t.co/oWBVZ0b8yh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Come bring me your softness... and then I found it :-D > Billy Preston & Syreeta - 1981 http://t.co/LVZ0jHFIJW #memory		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Steven G. Yantis died on June 21. A great Psychology & author of seminal papers on Visual Perception and Attention http://t.co/8HsYWV3t0k		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Very sad news > Steve Yantis, who studied visual attention, dies at 58 http://t.co/oTToVqWtkM #psychology		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username wow che reazione! plauso e inchino :-D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Remembering Steven Yantis > Abrupt visual onsets and selective attention: Voluntary versus automatic allocation http://t.co/6LbIkRKNHV		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#Italia by @username http://t.co/5eS5fg4XpY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#womeninscience Hedy Lamarr was indeed a scientist in her spare time and nobody could call her domain “soft science” http://t.co/TdyQYOKod3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wow come ti suono la superconduttività > How we created spooky experimental music in a superconductor lab http://t.co/uLX64nuGhf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Developmental psych needs funds > Psychology is weird, child psychology is much weirder @username http://t.co/nEHbQaMxgX via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interactive devices are helping people who have had a stroke to regain their motor function http://t.co/jU3BTbAZQ7 via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[APA Applauds Landmark Illinois Law Allowing Psychologists to Prescribe Medications http://t.co/mMSko8nXXh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Evviva! Jimmy Somerville is back > Smalltown Boy Reprise 2014: http://t.co/zqNwVDpnuZ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["@username: OK Go - Here It Goes Again - YouTube https://t.co/22KfOdyrja" #FFback		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Susie Wolff is ready for #F1 :-D "@username: Lego Susie! So cute. ???? http://t.co/8hnI5exvi5"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Simona De Silvestro is ready for #F1 :-D "@username: What a blast!!! I could get used to this.... #RoadToF1 http://t.co/IrvYHnDBMW"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Raccolti dai migranti/schiavi africani e venduti... in Africa > The Dark Side of the Italian Tomato: Web documentary http://t.co/3nIlRmTcPV		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Who can't go insane these days? Anybody can. Starting with me, Mr. Tichy.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[during my absence the press as well as TV had split in two.There are papers/programs that give all the news & those that give only good news		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Today a politician too must have a great voice, a great smile, and a great body to win voters over the television. Ijon Tichy		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[[1/2] It was a remote callotomy. I'm writing this too only pardy and with great difficulty, typing with the right hand.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[[2/2] The left I had to tie to the arm of the chair because it kept tearing the paper out of the machine. It wouldn't listen to reason...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Peace on Earth by Stanislaw Lem: The interstellar adventures of Ijon Tichy after his remote callosotomy. My post (IT) http://t.co/qoQJYKcP9R		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[US college drop-outs hit all-time high: half of all students don't graduate, mostly because they can't afford costs http://t.co/BBJl3R3qGW		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[In the occupied Gaza Strip children can take refuge & through music, forget about the siege & troubles around them http://t.co/LgVzy9dQhX		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Dark Knight of the Soul  http://t.co/vZfXJv8rZV  #meditation a lot of positive data & no mention of negative results or adverse effects		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Calabria amore e memoria>Speaking to My Father in a Dead Dialect http://t.co/0N8At7mRp3 “ti vo’ pigliare ’na shcuppettata”/“may you be shot”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[E dopo Bohemian gravity... :-D Fantastico! > A Capella Science - Rolling in the Higgs (Adele Parody): http://t.co/6H1pKZ8RlY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Can researchers track down the elusive successful psychopath or will the concept go down in history as clinical lore? http://t.co/ISSSbPiYhp		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Facebook "emotional contagion" Study: A Roundup of Reactions http://t.co/4sjz0PZ09h "bad science creeps me out more than the ethics"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How often do economists commit misconduct? A new study http://t.co/5DvndKi8il via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Internet's Own Boy: The Story of Aaron Swartz http://t.co/eBusgX1gUQ technology, civil liberties and awareness		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[“One should . . . be able to see things as hopeless and yet be determined to make them otherwise.” F. Scott Fitzgerald		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Electroceuticals spark interest http://t.co/8CLh31KvKl "Bioelectronic implants seem promising, but it is often unclear why they work"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username here a peer reviewed paper advocates for faith healers in the cure for schizophrenia http://t.co/cmhDMmTLpH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thank you! Yes, it's really "absurd"!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wow > Mindblowing anamorphic 3D drawings by Alessandro Diddi http://t.co/QbjeWzxtjF via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Guardian view on the end of the peer review http://t.co/4mGrsVp7z2 "peer review, it appears, is less reliable than it sounds"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Scientists threaten to boycott €1.2bn Human Brain Project http://t.co/HbQzGZqNSh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Archaeological Park of Sicilian Incompletion - Alastair Bonnett: My surreal trek through unfinished Italy http://t.co/2PvI0S8ivg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[We the undersigned members of the European neuroscience community are writing to express our concern w/ the course of the HumanBrainProject		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Open message to the European Commission concerning the Human Brain Project. Sign the Letter http://t.co/ipZYi7Ztxy		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis & the psychology of exorcism & possession, @username http://t.co/FGT2YjhF6g >future tragedies can be prevented w/ diagnosis		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Mr Renzi has signed a pact with the devil (Mr Berlusconi) > Charlemagne: Atwitter about Matteo Renzi http://t.co/411OBdSt7h via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Trouble With Brain Science: @username on Human Brain Project & Brain Initiative http://t.co/9p3FLRunw2 "amassing data is only a start"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[-26 hours Please Donate > #bow HQ print of the English autobiography of Maestro Giovanni Lucchi https://t.co/ZSpvbp5Fds #crowdfunding		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Do you know the new Academia Cremonensis? Now is online the application form for courses of violinmaking & bowmaking! http://t.co/ssnhkaeegv		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[1% of scientists publish a paper/year http://t.co/NOpTNicyCZ "the research system may be exploiting the work of millions of young scientists		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tasting, smelling and seeing... a glass of wine, please! > What We Really Taste When We Drink Wine http://t.co/q2cUoxOWeP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[At what age children begin the mental time travel? #episodicmemory Post (in IT) http://t.co/dJjp7XVsBF		]]></document>
</author>