<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="956f4dba-c26b-4f12-ae6d-f908c742cadc" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[Im tired and bored		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[IM HUNGRY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  yeah i'll be all biting my nails when to judges judge you and throw stuff at my bro when he talks		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Thats not true you have a really good voice		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  hahaha i know its his b-day in london but not here :( and why'd you reply it here?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HAPPY BDAY NIALL!! Love from one of your biggest fans. Hope i get to meet you. So how is your day so far? Great i suppose @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When someone calls me pretty me : Ha! no im ugly!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[recently told by the guy i like he might ask out my best friend :(  but on the bright side knowing her she wont say yes cause shes her		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  yeah tht be a good idea		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  haha course you do why am i not surprised		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ug boys why are they soo complicated		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When you notice that someone unfollowed you.. well ex-use me!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[when louis barfed me: LOUIIIISS My babby are you okay? *Leaning into to laptop*		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[enemy likes something Me: no i aint liking tht Louis likes the same think Me: *clicks like button*		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[:( My headphones just broke :( they were really good then all the sudden they just stopped :( #Dammit		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My cuz was like i know why you have a bunch a pics of louis im like why shes like cuz you like him and i was all NOOOOO #noshitsherlock		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My cuz " all i want for x-mas is my 2 weenies, my 2 weenies" Me : OMG!!! I THOUGHT I WAS BAD!! #Perv		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[haha lol watching this while doing my homework coudn't stop laughing   http://t.co/zFR2Ue6prF @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Im bored and tired and hungry  go life		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[gonna go watch tv now cause i want to :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Going to church @username 5 the service doesnt start till 6:30 but i volenteer sooo yeah		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just got back from church soaking wet (they had a giant bubble pit) Oh Eastlake Church the only church that has kids going home wet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When u like him but then he tells u he likes ur best freind :( life sucks at least i got @username Follow me Louis and make me smile		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Missing tht person when the entire time when there right in front off you , i miss her cause shes not my friend no more not cause shes gone		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["while im wide awake shes no trouble sleeping cause when a heart breaks no it dont break even" - @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I love you @username  Follow me please?  yeah i failed but im not much of a Photoshop expert  Hope you see it! http://t.co/FCuXzR4XdB		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[im going to find out who all the ppl that unfollowed me were and unfollow them back!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Have a bf now as of today but as i got home i started thinking am i really ready for this? Everyone told me bad things about him ,should i?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[you know how i posted about a bf well we kinda put a pause on the relationship because it was 2 akward		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[ugg life is compilcated right now no time for twitter		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[lol just had to put a dirty cup and a hair brush away i put the cup in the bathroom and the brush in the sink #epicfail		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[i hate it when ppl say they had  a blonde moment and im right there its like uhum whats that supossed to me *cough cough* @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username yeah you got tht last part right		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username hahaha not just tht i can imagine what goes through ur head " Today im going to randomly glue paper to kelsey's arm"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username yeah i have proof  @username  didnt petra glue a bunch a paper on my arm in bio		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  yeah joesph the guy sit next to REMEMBER..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  see we didnt get to do the debate in bio so i do a debate against you and i won !		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  in what SPANISH!! :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Eat Sleep Swim thts my life		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[there was DJ at my school today andso me and my freinds were the first ones who started dancing and the last to stop :P i looove dancing		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Are you serious got my report card today and my parents gave me a lecture cause i got 1 B the rest are all A's stupid parents		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hahaha me and louis got married today @username  your my husband now :P http://t.co/iNLxqQBMnH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[DO THE HUSTLE!! tht moment when i was the center of attention YEAH #popular		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  yeah but i couldnt put it on twitter :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I lost 3 followers recently and i know who they are thanks to http://t.co/AnGdGTF7Te		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["A bird only flies. It does not turn to another bird and ask, am I doing this right?" - Mary Anne Radmacher		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When ur in the middle of texting someone a long message and then they say bye so you have to erase everything to say bye		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[OMG IM SO HUNGRY BUT THERES NOTHING TO EAT		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Have a 4.0 GPA! HARVARD HERE I COME!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[1D's new leaked song Diana couldnt they have done one called kelsey!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  you leaked Just Cant Let Her Go and Diana why cant you just leak the entire album?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[my followers were growing fast and then when i hit 200 ive had 207 followers for an entire week WHAT HAPPENED!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I just found and unfollowed all my fake followings thanks to http://t.co/AnGdGTF7Te awesome app		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I thought all i needed was forgivness then i got it.. i still need more		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[people say eww 1D all they talk about is girls and love but no Diana is about depressed sucidal fans. They care about there fans.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[who wants to see nialls bum http://t.co/rqD7hRrOkd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Thts amazing!! I wonder if my dog could do tht!! http://t.co/TF85fhhWY1 #awesome		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[GOOD NIGHT!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[for all of those ppl who have unfollowed me i will now take back the follow i gave you in return of following me		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fun Fact : its annoying that some people think facts are fun		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[see being freinds with yourself on facebook is great to help you with games :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Teachers cause bladder infections because they don't let kids go to the bathroom		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[why im glad i only have brothers : my parents feel bad for me soo i got my own bathroom :P :) #icantakeaslongasiwant		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username OMG YOUR ON!! Liam i really do love you guys alot, it would mean the world to me if you would follow me!!! Please!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Liam!! I really love you and all of the band and it would mean the world to me if you would follow me! Please Liam ily		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username   thats how we know you care for your fans yet you do it with humor and thats why i love you Please follow me !!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  hope you read this ,hope you notice me, hope those crazy girls leave the snake area and i also hope  that you'd follow me		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username DO I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION!!!

I Love all of you and it would mean the world to me if you followed me! Please notice me !		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thats how we know you care about your fans but then it makes me crack up cause ur just so funny ily please follow me!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username ily ALOT and  my dream is to be a lawyer and my other dream is to be followed by you we can make both of these true!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  you and that tweet are PER-FECT and a follow from you will also be... follow me please??		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Close to 300 followers now!! Thank you @username !!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username really wish youd notice me but we all know thts not possible if you do follow me though well then youd turn my world around		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username ily i dont really know if you love me you dont really pay attention to me. I just hope id get a follow from you. :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  please follow me its all i want		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  i keep tweeting you cause i want you to notice me i want you to follow me thts it nothing else just for you to follow me		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Alright guys sorry for all the posts to liam now your probably annoyed by them but a girl gotta do what a girl gotta do but im done!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Good night you guys im done with the computer for today more tweets tommorow (not to liam dont worry)  #sleepwell		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Close to 300 followers!! Thank you eveyone soo much		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[that moment when your chatting on FB and you wanted to write how but you wrote hoe instead		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[studing for the SATs if i want to get into harvard i better start now		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My cousin is the most annoying one in the world http://t.co/X6UiemK0I8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Im officially married to louis cause it says so on facebook :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[qwertyuiop
asdfghjkl
zxcvbnm
 What idiot decided to put the letters on the keyboard in this order?  why not just abcd...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Answering the same letter three times or more in a row on a Scantron test is absolutely petrifying.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Whenever someone says “I’m not book smart, but I’m street smart”, all I hear is “I’m not real smart, but I’m imaginary smart”.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MapQuest really needs to start their directions on #5. Pretty sure I know how to get out of my neighborhood.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I find it hard to believe there are actually people who get in the shower first and THEN turn on the water.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[There’s no worse feeling than that millisecond you’re sure you are going to die after leaning your chair back a little too far.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why is vanilla ice cream white when vanilla extract is brown?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I love in horror movies how the person yells out “hello?!” as if the killer is gonna say “yeah I’m in the kitchen, want a sandwich?”		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wish I loved anything as much as rappers love female dogs and gardening tools		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I have officially bought the first batch of Halloween candies that will NOT make it to Halloween.#ilovecandy		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Repeat after me: it doesn't matter how big the problem is posting it on facebook wont solve it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If you look up "one" on google images one of the first few pics is One Direction		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I voted for Best Song Ever to make the #TeenNickTop10 countdown. Vote now! http://t.co/FcjhMItgeq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[going to yosemite tommorow packing up ugg then i have to go thru a 7 hour drive #bordum		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If the president were gay, would his husband be the first man?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If you were a genie and a person asked you this wish, "I wish you would not grant me this wish" what would you do?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Do movie producers still say lights, camera, and action when it is a dark scene?		]]></document>
</author>