<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="97999fdb-0754-4bf1-9dce-6f0cdec6558f" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[Snapchat: ximefr		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's no fun but I've been here before, I'm far from home and I'm fighting your war.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's better to feel pain, than nothing at all.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Who will love you? Who will fight?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I think I need to find a bigger place, cause when you have more than you think, you need more space.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Being an intellectual creates a lot of questions and no answers.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The way you move is a mystery...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Loving every minute cause you make me feel so alive, alive!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Everybody dance with the Peruvians https://t.co/5bsZxtVayb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's getting hard to be around you, there's so much I can't say, do you want me to hide the feelings and look the other way.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[She's up all night for good fun, I'm up all night to get lucky.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Take me to the place I love, take me all the way.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Loving you forever can't be wrong, even though you're not here, won't move on.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hoy gana Bayern, he dicho.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dicho y hecho.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Quiero jugar Among the Sleep ya!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[In the cut, in the cut... Rolling doobies up.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Now the drugs don't work, they just make you worse, but I know I'll see your face again...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username awwww ya pronto chulls #FinDeSemanaCool #NoVoyAEstudiar :D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Me voy a ir al infierno.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[¡A mucha honra, Montserrat de Barreal soy! ?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[And all those conversations are the secrets that I keep...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I find your lips so kissable and your kiss unmissable, your fingertips so touchable and your eyes... Irresistible.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Valley girls giving blowjobs for Louboutins, what you call that? Head over heels		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[BYE PIZARRO, ERES TODO UN CSM!!! TE AMO WEBONASO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[GANAMOS CSM!!!!!!!!! BIEN PERU BIEEEEN PTM LLORO LLORO SE ME SALE TODOOOOO!!! BIEN CARAJOOOO LA COSA ES GANAR!! BIEEEN VAMOSS <3<3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HashtagNoSéComerComoMontse HashtagMontseNoQuierePlato		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[They don't know about nosotros.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Heartache doesn't last forever, I'll say I'm fine...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[But now you'll never know, baby, I loved you first! #Uchala #TePelaste #PosMeMato		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm the Scatman.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Who says we need a plane, when we can use our minds.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm a lover and I'm a sinner, I play my music in the sun. I'm a joker, I'm a smoker, I'm a midnight toker.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I was so happy we had met, it was the age of no regret.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[ALM ase mucho no uzo Twitter xD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just stop, you worry to much, you ain't always gotta know just why or when or what.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I want you and your beautiful souuuul.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I always put you number one in my life.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[And I'm the one that jaded you!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm still in love with you boooy *Enciende el porrito del amor*		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Doing the wrong things for all the right reasons.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wanna be where you are.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cool su boss eh @username @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Me mama Earth Wind & Fire y Kool & the Gang eternamente <3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Do you really want to hurt me? Do you really want to make me cry?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I want it knowing that you're walking away.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Love is strange, when there's beauty on the inside, the outside there's nothing to change.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I know it's hurting you, but it's killing me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Where I end and you begin.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's you and me, it's always been, And how I feel about you there's no end.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Living is easy with eyes closed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[One Direction está en Kansas... @username TE LARGAS A BUSCARLOS AHORA MISMO!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A heart of stone can turn to clay.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Open up your mind and you will feel it too, the sound, the touch, the thoughts, that you've been so blind to.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dream big or don't dream at all.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I've tried to ask myself, should I see someone else? I wish I knew the aaaanswer...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[And if our final day has come, let's pretend to carry oooon!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The only thing I ever wanted, was the feeling that you ain't faking.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'd rather be good than lucky.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fifty fifty.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Qué wonito eres :))		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So don't you ever for a second get to thinking you're irreplaceable?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Quiero ver a Never shout never aunque sea muy 2011 <33		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[On Saturday I know that you’re coming up to see me, when I go away things will change and you’ll never know it was easy.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[She don't call me one and only, she just calls me when she gets lonely, something I do gets her there so feel better and get well...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Perfect in every way, I see it in his face.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Act like I don't need her but... You, you're necessary. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No puedo creer que Ariana Grande sea novia de Jai Domenic <3 awwwwwwww dlahgaklsgñhslkghsaklgs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You got me right where you want me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's getting hard to be around you, there's so much I can't say, do you want me to hide the feelings and look the other way.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Money's a bitch that never sleeps.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I put my faith in something unknown.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So done with wishing you were still here.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When you feel so tired, but you can't sleep... Historia de mi vida.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hoy fui a Danoninear. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[SI AUUUUUUN TE AMOOOOOO SI AUUUUUN TE EXTRAÑOOO LOS DIAS SIN TI SON COMO MORIR, AUUUUUUUUU UH UH UH UH UUUN TE EXTRAÑO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[TSEA TOY EN CHOK!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Only you can fill that space inside... #IYKWIM		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Here I go again on my own going down the only road I've ever known		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[She's a slave to the rhythm.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Baby take me on a journey, I've been thinking lately, I could use a little time alone with you...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[And he doesn't give a damn about me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Lose yourself to dance.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Her-minion. http://t.co/QPBsEZYHjJ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[ME LLEVA LA CONCHA QUE ME PARIÓ. ALGUIEN HAGAME EL FAVOR Y MÁTEME.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[LARGATE ARANGO LARGATE CONCHA DE TU MADRE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[TOTAL, NI QUERÍA IR A BRASIL, ESTOY MAS MISIA QUE LA CONCHA!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Every little thing he does is magic, everything he do just turns me on.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[There's one life, one world, one chance and I don't wanna wait.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I hope you're not lonely without me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If I could spend the rest of my life with my people, I would do it over and over again.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[They tried to make me go to rehab but I said no no no...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username JEJE FAV.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So wake me up when it's all over, when I'm wiser and I'm older.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I speak a different language, but I still hear your call.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Is that what devils do?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Let me live that fantasy!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Take me to the place where you go, where nobody knows if it's night or day.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No inventes.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I think I'm falling for you.		]]></document>
</author>