<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="9f4836b6-5ba0-4523-a161-199c6ee97627" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[The hoe feeling so good that some niggas might kiss.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[With her top down screaming out: "MONEY AINT A THING"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username not sure if stupid or sacasm.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HAHAHAHA "@username: WHITE PEOPLE NEEDA CHILL FORREAL http://t.co/SMPrDaehHK"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[GIRL YOU GOTTA LET ME KNOW HOW YOU WANT THIS NIGHT TO GOOO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[OG is one who standing on his own feet, a boss is one who garantue we gone' eat.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: Women are good for 70 things.. Sandwich and 69."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: If I walk in and saw this I'll let bruh get his nut in before I kill him http://t.co/BH0KtBYgKF"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Most people be having long toes but small dicks.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This boy is on fire.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: i love when people try to hurt my feelings when i dont have any lmao"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I made something out of nothing, call me San Don the magician. She doing tricks with her pussy, I guess she's vagician.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Need a pussy that's hairless, I will French kiss it like we in Paris.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: Don't be a bitch, be the bitch."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: All these watches and still no time for you peasants ????????????? http://t.co/4s90FYCaPj"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: RT if you see a set of keys you want ???? http://t.co/RS8KsWCmnA"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: Thissss... Would solve a lot of problems http://t.co/Z7dm2CTKEh"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: hearing a story thats obviously made up http://t.co/QLt0l2ENhn"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When girls say "Don't play the game cause I can play it better" is like telling me your hoe intentions are ready to come out at any moment.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[We are not one and the same, nigga I'm fucking insane. Fuck is you saying? Your ass been doing same shit.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Highclass but surrounded by these low-lifes.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Shots fired, suspect speared off.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Need a ride and die chick that stay loyal to my dick. She need to know that I am working hard and I ain't coming home at six.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Righting all my wrongs, for these homies out there thugging.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Shots fired.. another gone, I feel that man's pain. Daddy said my down and said "that came with the game".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: me whenever I see dogs ???? http://t.co/ioIkJqXtsX"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thanks, I appriciate it!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[De Champions League is terug! http://t.co/WBmWsEoFvz"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: my least favorite animals are children"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Talking about Marie, she chilling with Molly.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Then she said she's pregnated, that's the night your heart died. Now you gotta go to your girl and report that.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Main reason 'cause your pastor said you can't abort that. Now your driver says that new Benz.. you can't afford that.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[All that cocaine on the table, you can't snork that. Dat going to the money that the court got, all out on the allemony.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["@username: Arsenal looking for the Danny Welbeck receipt. http://t.co/gRDgc6CwsP"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: When we all become fathers #YesAllMen http://t.co/c0UoqfFKrq"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HAHAHA "@username: How girls walk to the bathroom after you nut in them... http://t.co/3X4gmQud1t"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[WAT EEN SCHÖNE GOAL!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  "@username: These hoes ain't loyal http://t.co/0i4MYKAKA9"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[IK GA STUK ???????? http://t.co/CzzdcrHU7N"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: NIGGA DIED WHILE HE WAS CRANKIN THAT SOULJA BOY LMFAO http://t.co/5M9jMbmyJt"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Did i allow u to have fun without me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm nice to the weird kid, so he'll spare my life when he snaps		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I will do a lot of things but admitting im cold to my mum who told me to bring a jacket isn’t one of them		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tweets on fire but the blunt ain't.. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[10 TO 10 REMIX MOVIE PAID FOREVER		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[THEY SAY THAT I CHANGED... YEAH CHANGED LIKE I SUPOSSED.Q		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[IMA BOSS - MEEK MILL FT. RICK ROSS ????????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[GOT SO MANY SHADES THEY THOUGHT I HAD A LAZY EYE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Let me take take you to home comming, so I won't be alone at home, cumming.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[All up in your hood like a food stamp.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[All the freaks know that I'm a true champ. She finna drop it low on SVO's bootcamp.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[She a fan, that's fantastic.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Before I fall in love, i'm prepared to leave her.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: Hiding your favorite food from the rest of your family because you're a selfish motherfucker."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I don't really care what everybody gotta say.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: have u ever introduced two friends to each other and they started hanging out without u? like i made u what u are wtf?!"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[She at home comming, while i'm at home cumming.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[WHO YOU CAME WITH? I TELL HER FUCK THAT NIGGA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: A MILF is a sexy ass mom over 35. If you're 20, you're just a slut with a baby."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username close enough http://t.co/4huIoXtjMh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I like these bad bitches, from a decent home.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If you leave this time I feel that you be gone for good so no hold on like leaves and fall to what is left.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Autumn Leaves - Chris Brown ft. Kendrick Lamar.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If my ship go down who will abort?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I keep my feelings in a safehouse, better that I don't speak.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm confused to who I'lI spend my forever with.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[They say life is a bitch but I'm well prepared cause Marie Jane is a better hoe.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  100 - Leeuwin completed 100% of his 31 passes vs FC Groningen & won all 3 of his aerial duels. Perfect. http://t.co/DRJvz14ur8"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username she fucked a horse? Wtf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username also a beautiful girl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I feel that you be gone for good.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username cant handle it already?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This could be us but you playing... http://t.co/ZTJscWeeBF		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Free your mind let your consious free.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HAHAHA "@username: Rt if you were inspired https://t.co/02F7pAou5S"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'LL WAKE UP WORKING LIKE A MEXICAN, DAT MEAN I WORK FROM 10 TO 10.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username nice pics when its blurred, noobs.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[WHO SAID YOU CAN'T FIND LOVE IN THE CLUB? CAUSE I WANNA TELL THEM THEY'RE WRONG.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[New flame ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[August Alisina - Downtown ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: people need to understand that I'm joking 99.9% of the time"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Runaway train, never going back.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Somehow im not even here nor there.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: For me it was "I just need a person".. http://t.co/22nxl7D2nU"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: When you call shotgun but end up in the back = http://t.co/IyqyaO7QkL"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Chris Brown - Add Me In. ????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Chris Brown - X (album) ????????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I am absolutely positively, even though I'm sick and tired I get busy.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Drink om half 12 al een flesje cola, it's all about perspective.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[August Alsina - Make It Home ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username we have this Dutch saying "om je vingers bij op te eten", which means the same as the Chinese translation.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I can see from this high up, you ain't got a heart girl.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just put your hands in the air if you're missing somebody...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Come home..., I can't handle this alone.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Have you ever lost someone? Tried to take it back.. but the damage is done.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When you make mistakes the most, some day it will make you grow.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username @username see that jesus cross? She praying for bigger tits but it aint helping.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Netflix in de bus, BAM, knallen, jonguh.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hahahah het programma Extreem wtffff		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Reach for the stars, so if you fall you'll land on a cloud.		]]></document>
</author>