<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="b38fee80-2fb1-4481-be25-e8297aae928d" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[Everyday I come up with a new optimum solution. It proves optimum is only dependent on the time		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: @username Aap KYA LAG RAHE HAIN Don 2 mein .. God bless you! Can't wait to see the film :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Worst thing about FB and twitter is you can follow someone without actually "follow"(literally)-ing him or her.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Someday we all have to say "good bye". Why on earth we think somebody as my own?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It is always complicated. Just want to live a simple life. Is that wrong?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[12789 seconds.. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[PockeTwit.. nt bad..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Getting mor n mor tech-savy.. someday I'll cease to exist as a human.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Friday the 16th is here... :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hey.. tum bore to nehi ho rahi na...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Is it necessary to have a last minute glitch?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[And here we go...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Enjoying the sun and the sea... :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Updated location... :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/O01LjQTc loving it		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[fantastic two days.. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Chori chori seenay se saansein,
Chori chori le gayi chura ke,
Chori chori khwaabon me aake,
She got me loosin my mind...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ready with Don 2, this Saturday, 9am Kulraj Broadway.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[17057 seconds!!!!!!! crazy man.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Unfollowing @username . You'll be always the guide of my life how to stay evergreen and young all life.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why am I tensed??		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Nariman Irani the producer		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Come to "Don 2" Tomorrow from 9:00 am to 12:00 pm. http://t.co/xLJJAI7v		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hectic life.. busy schedule.. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The last week of an eventful year. And ending with a twist. A new begining I guess.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[That was the biggest mistake of my life. Yes I made mistake and only myself to blame for it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Each of them was mistake. And I cannot argue about it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[And now the dice is rolling once again. Only someone from future can tell me if I am getting into the same problem once again. I hope not.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My fav Pappa @username has taken Vardhaan to a new height. If Don was grt, Vardhaan was the perfect  antagonist.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: i smell victory. #Aus179/8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[All tweples are insomniac. I want to sleep as well.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hence it is proved Parliament is the process to keep the Democracy out of pollitics. A shame.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The last day. Take the good things and forget the not so good ones. But dont forget your enemies.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A very happy and prosperous new year to all. Welcome 2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[18315 sec. it shud be the limit dude.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Now my most dreaded number is 502, followed by 401 and 400.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username Did beer on the pitch make the ball bounce high? An exposé tonight exclusively on 161 All Out FM		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's still alive, and me too. I just hope to sleep well and keep myself away from all problems.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username why don't u try? #bleedBlue #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username RT @username: RT @username: Block Rushdie. Block Google. Block Facebook. Blockheads		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I support #wikipediablackout! Show your support here http://t.co/n012Hx2J		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Total confusion....... To do or not to do, and to do what...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Strange to see people react that way. Do they only care when they face trouble themselves?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[What do I hate most? Someone lying. Disgusting...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Problems problems everywhere...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why is my throat dry when my eyes are full of tears?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If twitter was not here, my life ud have atleast one less problem... :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tired.. Damn tired... My weekend is being delayed more and more...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When you spend most of the day in office, you will know that you are upto something.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Twitter changes again... not bad though..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Love is a lost art.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So many days with all different names. Does the "Love day" exist? I think that is missing in the merchandising of products.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Late enough for a sleep.. But so many things to do still.. I am enjoying my late nights at office.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[5 students now. May be I should be prepared with some proper syllabus now.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Measuring the depth of life...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Feeling the need for a long holiday. But have to listen to him who never stops doing his job.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I think it is high time to forget and forgive.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If you don't trust your lover, you are not confident of yourself.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The more you want to hold onto something, the more you risk loosing it. Love is no exception.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Loosing your cool for nothing is not a good thing.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[6th student here with unique problem. May be it is easier said than solved.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Miracles doesn't happen nowadays. We have to make them happen.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[For the moment I need a break from my life.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My weakness makes me stronger. That does not mean it goes away.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Meeting old friends always brings back memories... Good ones ofcourse.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Body wins against brain. A rare for me.. Feeling damn tired and need for rest.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Finally got something I have longed for a long time.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tired of the second best options.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A day when the Guru needs some advice...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Bengal beats Mumbai with the leadership of our captain Saurav Gangully  and fantastic performance of Laxmi..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Life is full of surprises and we must be ready for them.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just looking into the comments of friends in a photo after marriage of two of our friends, I am sure it... http://t.co/wWPyIamj		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Beauty is just the wrapper, the person inside is the real gift.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A point of no return approaching very soon. Tensed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It feels bad when I know some bad news about someone but cannot tell him/her. But that hardly is my fault.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Last 9 days. Tensed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It has always felt better to be reconnected with old friends. Forgetting the past and moving onto the future.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Coming to end of a almost non stop journey from yesterday. and that is in bus. no sleep in last 33 hours. Need some urgently.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A timeless day. 10hrs sleep after 40hrs gap and 14 hrs of journey in the dusty roads in between.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I like to play with fire, but am I old now to stop playing?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's very very the last the day. Counting the final hours my buoy...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[End of a wonderful journey? Well atleast as of now.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If somebody told me this just this sunday morning, I wud have lughed at him. But am I bitten by the bug again? It... http://t.co/k2uS055Z		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why do people think love as reason to live rather than just another part of life?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Can love happen second time?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dilemma: I never knew the meaning better.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This the cartoon that angered CM http://t.co/iK37riJ5		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I just like the special dose of vitamin (only if it is as smooth as today's).		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Every morning I lie to me when I get up and it stays with me throughout the day.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The score after a long time: 38-1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A day that may be remembered for years (for good or bad).		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Madly or badly, it is always deadly.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sarat is here. http://t.co/EXa30zEW		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Another one. http://t.co/ZC8IF8cp		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Feeling lonely after a long time... Maybe I need someone with me when I am happy. Didn't feel so while I was going through a tough time.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tar gun gun moner gan bristi namay, 
top top fota pore onekhon. 
Sei bristi veja more dak diyeche, 
veja kak hoye thak amar mon		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username if u trust don't be confused.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It is simply 'IMPOSSIBLE'		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Darker than the clouds...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Ctrl" is the 'key'-word of the moment.		]]></document>
</author>