<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="b3ff1402-beab-4395-a107-56e5fb19c0e9" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[My body feels taut I'm wound so tight. Think ill smoke a bowl and relax some before I try and crawl into bed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Aches and pains and pains and aches.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[That's the end of that.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Charm her		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Leg and joint pains that even a bowl can't shake.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Watching #takesfromthecrypt ???????? #bordelloofblood		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cause deep down you know that it's Edgar Frog of the Frog brothers #catchthatreference		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Letting my hair dye sit. This part always takes forever.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[2 chainz in this episode of #svu?? Epic!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I think it's about time to grow up and start trying to put some effort into life again.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Love when I get stoned enough to style my hair <3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I can't tell what you're thinking.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Smiling cause this song will always be one of ours.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Playing Soul Calibur 4 with the guys! :) #ps3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bowls and video games with my guy and his best friend #greatafternoon #summertime #soulcalibur4 #ps3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm not ready to be broken again.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I don't know what to do right now.....		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm eating my head		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[3-4 hours of work left and I just want to curl up and pretend the world doesn't exist.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm honestly just barely holding on right now.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hoping for the best, expecting the worst #always		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Seen on fence "beauty will save the world"
"Pft, fuck that."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm watching #ShinobiHeartUnderBlade on #GetGlue http://t.co/r7UIKIokGK		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photoset:  http://t.co/b5efeNj326		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photoset:  http://t.co/rybL76m5zU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photoset: alifelongromance: quixoticandabsurd: ataritastic: rifa: lady-fett: therealkristycarlisle:... http://t.co/0c9z4VCwZ3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photoset:  http://t.co/q55UXHw18F		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photoset:  http://t.co/KZZkzkfmiN		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo: musicsumo: My ring is thiiiiiis big! (at State Of The Ark Thrift Shop) http://t.co/OE5J4CG9zR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photoset: discoveringfeminism: deforest: Joan Crawford in Possessed (1931) 82 years later and it’s still... http://t.co/UEspT2QVGk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Overheard: Straight Person: But who pays for the date? Queer Person: No one. We dine-and-dash, cackling as... http://t.co/KZISWGZfyq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo:  http://t.co/V89KzDU8oX		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photo:  http://t.co/2naxnG98o9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Photoset: vukizzle: Gonna go see this tomorrow!! http://t.co/JJUMRVZcYV		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm watching #TheWarriorsWay on #GetGlue http://t.co/VYiFmAmjD9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Had it since it came out, but I'm finally sitting down and playing #thelastofus!!! #ps3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Put on pants to make breakfast? What for?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Left me a hit ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Watching #blacksnakemoan before I hop along to work. One of my favorites!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck me, this soundtrack is godly ?????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[At work a half hour early ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'll dream that you mean me, even though I know that time is already past and gone		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You still cross my mind so much		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Soo hungry. I feel like that's becoming the status quo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm watching #Zulu on #GetGlue http://t.co/AGqzAjMHSb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wish they'd stop fucking up the schedule over at the cinemas		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Burn it slow to maximize the smoke		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm watching #ButterflySword on #GetGlue http://t.co/7RKbwB1x1v		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wish I had another hit left.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Headed to work early for some extra hours #moneyhungry		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Making the first bus>>>		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cleaning around the house.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Having a Snow White moment.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It feels like you rarely pick up when I call lately...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I know what you say you're up to, but lets face facts; I'm still wondering.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm running on 3 hours of sleep and been kicking ass all day; my last theater doesn't get out till 2:11am and I've got a bikeride home still		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Stealing a break, cause I'm beat #exhausted #worktweet #allaboutthebenjamins		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I won't lie. I wish you'd text me more...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[To my coworker who barricaded me in the supply closet while I was getting restock.... You're ducking hilarious, James #worktweet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I dunno if it's more irritating that I have 2 theaters left or that I have to wait 20 minutes before I can hit the next one #worktweet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username yeah I really enjoy the job, just not enjoying the movie schedule right now lol		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Annnddd waiting on my final theater -.-  #planaheadbetter #tipsformanagment #latenight #worktweet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[First time getting stuck at the train tracks on my ride home #biketweet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's hard to admit, I trust you less and less all the time.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Probably have no reason to be, but I have to admit, I'm more than a little hurt.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Contemplations of kindness that will kill you.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck this day, I'm ready for the next one.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#nowwatching #GhostAdventures instead		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wiping down, washing up, baking. The usual. #productivestoner		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I guess the truth is that I'm not expecting much from you at this point.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I should not have to pick up your slack if I'm getting paid less than you #worktweet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Not that I mind the ride home...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Damn, had no idea how late/early it is. Guess I got lost playing #tombraider #ps3 #gamergirl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Utterly ambivalent.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bout to take a rip and fold some laundry. Time to get shit done.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[On some other level right now		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Coconut cookies, mango Mochi ice cream, and pork bones for the dogs. Fuck yeah.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bout to get dressed, rip the rest if this bowl and hit up target real quick so I can get on these pies.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username lol!!! Key Lime and strawberry. I'm practicing for a pie contest that's coming up on the 14th :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Recently I've made: coconut cream, coconut custard, strawberry, blueberry, strawberry-blueberry honey, and a pecan pie.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Next up: Key Lime pie and another Strawberry pie.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Made a "southwestern" style lasgna last night, Tex Mex Italian came out pretty fucken proper. #stonerfood #nomz #munchies		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wish this ps3 update wasn't taking so long -.-		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Flying so fucken low tonight.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bus driver is super impressed with how I handle the bike rack like nothing #fitliving ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Despite that it's completely possible, I can't believe that my laundry is done drying already.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Guilty pleasure? Watching #JerseyShore #cantlie		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Got switched from day to night shift. Sweet ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Home before I was even scheduled to be off #fuckyeah		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Rode like the fucken wind #bikelife		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Woooow to guys at work who just don't take the hint ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hello July.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I hateeee being cold		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Terrified to trust.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wish I could remember where I put my nail polish -.-		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Painting my nails. Still trying to decide how to do them for 4th of July though ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Morning Romp. 
Cyrus enjoying his backyard ???????? #mornings #pitbull #rednose http://t.co/Zs7AVbTl0Y		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My dog is really just holding a stick in his mouth and running laps around our back yard. How can I bottle and sell this?!?!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fml. Missed my first bus so now I'm gonna be 20 minutes late to work, unless someone who can give me a ride wakes up.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Caught "World War Z" this morning, was pretty interesting. Leaving in a bit for "This Is The End" #cinemalife		]]></document>
</author>