<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="bde7a38f-fd87-4777-a954-d3ec34873d8a" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[Made south western lasagna and a strawberry pie last night. #texasliving		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for my paycheck!!! I'm jonsing for some pizza hard core!! #stonergoals		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My kingdom for a New York slice. #munchies #homesick #pizza ???????? #eastcoast		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Can't explain it but I feel so unfulfilled tonight.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bedtime at my house is like a children's book 
Goodnight Colter????
Goodnight Carson ????
..... Goodnight Moon....????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Got the laundry done ???? finally time to crawl into bed and try for some sleep  thinking ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Getting a ride from one of my roomies to the domain an hour before work to run errands ???? #winning		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[That 10 hour shift was way rough last night, now getting ready to pull some extra hours at the game shop cause I'm all about that cash????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm watching #DantesInferno on #GetGlue http://t.co/8DLvQ4j3LQ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[God it's so slow today (minus these 2 theaters that have like 40 people per)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ready for a smoke and then I think I'll be ready to finally tackle this trifle		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sitting at work waiting for my xenergy drink to kick in.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[God I hate the cleaner manager over at the cinema's. what a pretentious prick		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Leaving my GA with the instructions to "guard" #worktweet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[2 1/2 hours to freedom.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Craving chipotle so bad		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Maybe I should have gotten food instead of makeup during my break #girlproblems		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hungry enough that it tastes like I've been chewing on a balloon.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Got offered the bar back position here at the cinema ????????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Been at this job about 4 months and I got offered the job that most people are gunning for just by minding my own.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tbh I got nominated for this job being that at least 2 bartenders requested me by name when asked who they might want.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Late night solo rips.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is just how I roll		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it takes all of 10 minutes for me to cycle through 12 different versions of myself.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wonder if she realizes her make up looks like a mimes?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I think it's time for another bowl.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Not the news I wanted to hear ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[7 pm can not come fast enough... Not like I'll be home till about 10:30		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ughh I am so exhausted		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Trying not to fall asleep in the car.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Creepers? That's that shit I don't like!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Feel the world beneath your feet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sorry. Silly me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck over analyzing.... And while I'm at it... Fuck my life too ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's often hard to tell if I'm being overly paranoid or overly trusting.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username sorry but I didn't post the ad that I'm credited with on your page.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I hate people who just act like my dog is dangerous just cause he's a pitbull. Fuck y'all.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The werewolf vs the vampire woman lol		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Oh god. Not sure what's wrong but all my joints from my mid back down hurts so fucking bad. Hopes these tokes of THC help.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Put on "The Possession" and now the whole crew has been sucked in.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Listening to Devendra Banhart while watching the clouds slide over the moon.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just got my first barback schedule ????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wanna shank this bitch from work.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Touch up day		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So glad it's warm out tonight :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["My 'No' means 'No', my 'Yes' means 'Yes'. And my 'Maybe' means 'Get the hell out'" #madea		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Get pelted with munchies		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[First day as barback today. Way nervous, but excited! ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cant believe I put my phone through the wash -.-		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Omg, finally!!! I cant wait!! “@username: Season 8 starts on the 16th"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to have a phone again!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Uugh, wish I could figure out why I feel so sick		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Was gonna wait down here, cause its warm, till I realized I have 3 minutes till 4:20 #bongwardbound		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It left a bad taste in my mouth, but an amazing buzz in my blood.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ahh good to have a phone again		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Money in my pocket, fat stacks in my wallet.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hearing my life philosophy in a song		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I can't believe how much people back home be on Facebook -.-		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[God damn my bong needs a cleaning		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If I could have any power it'd be the power of suggestion.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just a fuck up		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Landlord will be here to replace our ac in about an hour and 10		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Conversations on the destruction of the prank call.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[An hour till the next theater and most of my side work is done. That's how you spell B-O-R-E-D.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Do what you will but please don't shut me out.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dreams of some day wearing a white dress.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[We drift inside each other, all we have is one another.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[With Jacob #EvilDead #GetGlue http://t.co/FACCgqkkNS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A clean bong hits like a sexy bong #truth https://t.co/VF9eP9ig1j		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cause you know I'm still at it #builtforthis #girlswhosmokebongs #nofilter http://t.co/QCo0UVsjKo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I love when people think they get what I'm saying but have no clue. Way to presume.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm an insomniac, who suffers from night terrors working 3 jobs, working 7 days a week. Uninterrupted sleep is like fucking gold to me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Oh my fucking god my back is killing me. Must be time for a bowl and morning yoga.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Did I mention I've accomplished flipping from a handstand into a bridge pose as well as a drop back into a bridge		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Now I've just got to learn to go the other way. Lol.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Smoking fat bowls before we go catch "Two Guns"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[All in my hair.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I need a massage. Mmm back neck shoulders and feel please!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sooo my coworker kissed me on the cheek yesterday when he gave me a hug goodbye. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[So fuckin glad to be home with my bong and my dude		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Well I can hear the baby bird that I found the eggshell for that's above my walkway/ outside my window		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bout to get high and play me some Skyrim before bed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[On that keeping my bong clean grind		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Restless yet Exhausted		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Can't even concentrate on that right now and in no way shape or form do I know what to say, so I'll just eat my fruitypebbles n smoke a bowl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No more excuses, it's time to get back in shape.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I've been telling myself this all summer but have been through so many changes. Enough is enough though. Good luck girl!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I have a new # by the way but send me yours and ill hit you up w. it and we can be workout support buddies lol!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Trying to figure out a good way to organize this, but I think the best way is to jump in and sort it out as I get more comfortable.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I run and walk every day. I'm not out of shape. But I need to start actually working out again cause I used to be in Better shape		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thanks, and I'm honestly into HIIT more though lol. I just run for a couple miles a day, and bike twice a week, but I need to get		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username my HIIT back in there and get consistent with my yoga, cause I just practice moves lately rather than full flows.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Have the bus very much Not to myself today lol #ebbandflow		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck Traffic ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Maybe got a new bed? Guess I'll see when I get home tonight.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tired from all this effort.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The ride home is so much smoother with a full front tire :) ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If I told you I was lonely, would you want to get close and hold me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[There's a fuck ton of stuff in my garage.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Resistant to change #TaurusRising		]]></document>
</author>