<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="be1f9286-68c1-4864-b269-4b6de3b8b7eb" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[Yawn.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username You're welcome man :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm out.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Ether >>>> Takeover		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["There will be tears, I have no doubt, there may be smiles but too few, and when those tears have run out, you'll be numb and blue"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Mad at the world		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Michael Irvin als Daylyt http://t.co/waJuoRdAkv		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Having a Break in Bed like Walter White		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Niggas straight kill me, knowing that they pranksters, this is going out to you sex offenders"*		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Okayyyy so Asians can't handle booze @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username That's not what you said yesterday.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username That's the way you like it right?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Lovecrimes - Frank Ocean		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I told myself I wouldn't flip I made a little bit, I'm no magician but I hope this Blue Dolphin do the trick"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Fuck biting, try writing		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ignorance is bliss so I'm happy slapping dumb fuckers.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[3 months ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Till Dawn - The Weeknd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["The blacker the berry is, the more sour the fruit"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Laylow - CirKus		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Good Morning - Kanye West		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Got to stay strong.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pass the designated driver the key, and don't worry, drinks on me, so have a toast with me		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Who killed chivalry, they need to get their sentencin'"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Burn It Up - R. Kelly ft. Wisin y Yandel, nostalgiaaaa		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Cause I show love, never get the same outta niggas, guess it's funny how money can make change outta niggas"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Best handig om  "You Might Also Like"-friends te hebben. New music can make my day.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ugh.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Sometimes I feel like I'm just being pulled apart, from each one of my limbs, by each one of my friends" 8 Mile - Eminem		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Never forget the love I have for you.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Love for the ones who prove themselves to be real family, like @username <3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Controverse gives fame what it needs.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username You know what it iyyis		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Jeffrey is Zwarte Piet racistisch? TELL ME NIGGA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[AAAAAAAAAAAAIGHT Childish Gambino's nieuwe album uit in December. The Community will love it. Slow it down..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Tell me that you need me
Tell me that you want me // HA, GAAAYYYY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username Out of your age category, viespeuk.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[People turning blind eyes to sorrow.. Get real.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA['97 Bonnie And Clyde - Eminem, relating		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just the two of us, just the two of us..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I will never fall, I just want it all.." Still a great song @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username 3 years and you're still responding to your fans. Respect.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Come on man, she just wants to be noticed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[These girls ain't got nothin' on you.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  Thanks!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hier is ie dan Cees! Let your followers know ???? http://t.co/Zrn0LVE4Nh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Nothing personal.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Mikado met Ethiopiërs, who's in?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Stay Jersey Shorin'		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wow, shivers.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Random burst of happiness!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[IK WIL CHILDISH GAMBINO'S EN HOPSINS NIEUWE ALBUM WHAAAAA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[White Dress - Kanye West		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Gooooood morning Vietnam!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Yes, One Direction ARE Children in Need...

...of a good kick in the balls.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ciao, Min.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I wanna be an emo, I wanna be popular, I wanna get a life, I wanna be MADE!"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Yeah I know it gets hard, but we made it this far, and we never gonna stop, even if we reach the top of our dreams"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It bothers me when the gods get to actin' like the broads		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username JE LAAT NICOLE IN DE STEEK GODVERDOMME		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Morning blessings to you too!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wish I had that About Time power.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Always on the edge no Randy Orton		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Good night cruel world, I'll see you in the morning..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Taking care of me.. You're the greatest <3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Somebody better tell 'em that we in this bitch like an unborn baby" Fabulous bars <<<< Dope track though		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Woodmorning, no turn that around		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Porchlight - Big KRIT ft. Anthony Hamilton		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["You taught me how to feel, when nobody ever would, and you taught me how to love, what nobody ever could"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I know man, NWTS tour. Best bruut!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's like six milli ways to die my nigga choose one		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username TWEET BATTLES TWEET TWEET BATTLES... TWEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEET		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Rage Valley - Knife Party		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[maar dit keer was de top comment: "Was looking for Eminem.. Don't regret listening to this."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck yeah.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Yu-Gi-Oh World Championship Tournament 2004 tot ik in slaap val. Fock jullie.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[TAIFAIHBUY: Thank Allah It's Friday And I Haven't Blown Up Yet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Put your money where your mouth is.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Right now I'd have to agree with most women out there and admit that Paul Walker is probably quite hot.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Maar for real, RIP to a fast and furious legend.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[2 Fast 2 Swerve		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Daaaayumn, The Raid 2 trailer looks sick! http://t.co/iQTSsoeoCJ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Belong To The World is gewoon haunting.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Focking stoommachines!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tricks up my sleeve http://t.co/7eY6eRuAEl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Rest In Peace Mandela, ik vond je heel goed in Bruce Almighty en the Shawshank Redemption.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Skin And Bones - Foo Fighters		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Wrecking Ball  van Miley Cyrus		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Hardcore to the koffieboon als Max Havelaar"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I installed it via xSellize, Insanely just showed 2.3 even after I deleted and re-added. iFile installed but couldn't find app		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username You're welcome! Hope that the insanelyi repo will be fixed soon, I'll support Movie Box any way I can		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nice to meet you, I'm the luckiest boy in the world.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I love the smell of IDGAF in the morning.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Brickleberry is mooi.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Aight beter word ik featuring		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The only thing you shouldn't underestimate about yourself is your ego.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Diamonds should be a bitch's best friend, appreciate us.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bed, even though we're miles apart, you'll always be in my heart.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just like the lady that visits me while I'm asleep in that bed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Radio unfriendly music >>>>>		]]></document>
</author>