<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="c7537d18-440b-451a-991a-22cb30f28d3a" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username I finally got it!!  It just took a minute (that's why I'm not proud!!!) - You are an angel in your spare time!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Ain't nobody just one thing"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username you are blood kin w @username -deaths from her food decreasing-though I suspect Nurse K just knows how bring them back now?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username How can that be? You are Perfection and movies are great!! oh- is this like a threat? I am SO going to movie w/you #BringIt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username exciting news about  @username He's GREAT addition to @username! TN fans happy to have him back and keep up w/him!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Oklahoma to visit UTC wrestlers | Times Free Press http://t.co/qbnbHFNtqL		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Have a great day moving in your old-pal-new-roommate!  Welcome to @username @username! #WOSBO http://t.co/3PGH6eGTNc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Wow.... Sad day for Mocs, but Congratulations and proud for you and your family.  You will be great and bless a lot of people!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username - Housecoats are sexy - and timeless!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pentagon Spokesman says they know of about 300 Americans currently fighting w/ISIS in Syria-who all have visas to come back to USA-What?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username -Thank you, Rocco - I needed this -and - I'm on it!! http://t.co/Md4e5tGC7X		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Coach S-Can't wait to WATCH YOU GUYS GO!Officially my 2nd favorite D1 team following #Chattanoogawrestling w/son @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["That bunny was scary" @username the morning after watching Donnie Darko.  #SoCute #BunniesAreScary		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username "Benavidez will have his hands full w/ D. Ortiz who absorbed only 24 strikes in his last 2 fights" #DustinOrtiz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username got 7 new followers in just the last 3-4 days, but hasn't tweeted since 10/2013.  That's impressive.  He's THAT good!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Yes, I DO! #ChattanoogaStrong is rubbing off on me! (Already have goals written out and hung up) --Thanks -and Yes, I Will!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#TBT @username Have a Great Day, John-John!!!!! http://t.co/G3DMZN7urE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  @username - apparently UT people bought 102,455 to their 800....  good times!  #CollegeWasFun		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username THEY MEAN THIS-I want to be scared! BUT I know"For God gave us a spirit not of fear but of power and love and self-control-2Tim1:7"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#TBT @username Why do you think he's so manly now? Taught him to shoot at 3 yrs old! You can compare this with your new pic-both so cute!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username for ur elderly peeps pls consider-#GoIrish I had to look gorish up-afraid name of sports injury! I am in no way proud of this!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username This will make you miss your #BigOrange and your Hillbilly roots if anything will!!!  #RockyTop @username @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Which cousin are you watching on ESPN?  Also, wonder why they didn't want me too?!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username USA does NOT negotiate with terrorists! We MUST NOT START! So hard, BUT we can NOT give in or we will lose ALL of our #FREEDOM		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username's out in open now-no denying it-Obviously they are serious &plan to destroy us...but they don't know our God yet!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username I see our boys having fun!  We need to follow Coach Dickson- so many cool UTC sports pics!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["It is the Lord who goes before you. He will be with you; he will not fail you or forsake you. Do not fear or be dismayed."-Deuteronomy 31:8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[2 KPD officers honored with medals Tuesday, 1 promoted to Captai http://t.co/FG0VNbwQ6e  Great Day for  some very deserving men!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username Katie, can you decode her emotions for me so I can send her a card?.........		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Have a Rugged Man wkend @username &@username!! AND Be Smart-Make Good Decisions @username at #RebelFootballGame! #iNagBecauseICare		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username where are the grown-ups in charge?? @username Did their #CharacterLogs make them hungry??		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YPsTc5qS3Y @username #TrendSetter Hey, Sister--thanks for help with your little brother!!  @username #MyFavoriteNurse		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Derrick and Turner- my heroes! http://t.co/oTZ38P6ODD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username #AllProsNoCons that's you!!!! http://t.co/Zixtu5vTgk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/xfrwKG54Xs  ilu @username Hope this makes you PROUD that I'm your mom!!! Tracey made it for my bday, but I am just awesome!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My God is the CREATOR of LIGHT!!!......He's also a BIG fan of the genre of dark comedy in my life- I'm pretty sure of this!!!  He is GREAT!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username rhymes with Nanny!!!--- TWIN DAY!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username HAPPY MONDAY! It was Awesome seeing your beautiful face this weekend! Have a #CHATTANOOGASTRONG WEEK-ILU http://t.co/ImPwvyx3x0		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username #ChattanoogaStrongBFF ROAD TRIP! We're invited- get the calendar! @username & @username ARE MISSING US! #WhoWouldNtBe?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Are you SURE it wasn't a young lady who couldn't help but stare because you are so Cute???!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#TBT a beautiful little girl and a brand new #Papaw  meet for the first time #iamPapumsBaby @username #GodIsGood http://t.co/oTAqG2Bydk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#TBT -- Happy October!! @username http://t.co/CYYXGvHYI2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#TBT @username - remember this? A new baby and a new UncleJack? #LongHairDontCare J, I hope your day is "school"!! http://t.co/xNujksTFrc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/ICtwk7Xcbt @username - Here's some good news!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I NEVER DO TBT's & I'm sad! I REMEMBERED TODAY! YAY!!! ...I've just been told it's Wednesday. #MomProblems  @username @username @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[SHRADER BROTHERS IN KNOXVILLE TODAY!! @username @username @username @username #GoVols Have fun boys!!! Ilu! http://t.co/zud4dEoOv5		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Heart-Breaker!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I have 2 college teams I am loyal to -UTC wrestling and UT Football!  I may have to give you the stink-eye at BallnBrawl :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I forgive you and I still love you and every ChattStrong Wrestler!!!!...... See you Friday!  (maybe no stink eye now!!)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username and I were just talking about you looking good in your pink shoes!  I think T should get some too!  #GoBurros		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username HOLD UP! You're killin' me, Smalls!  T & I agree-YOU are BIGGEST UT FAN we know!! We all have to give B. a HOT MINUTE-He's Close!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username All fair-weathered fans will be back soon-I KNOW YOU-You won't want them sitting in your SECTION much less allowed to wear orange		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Power Out! @username made me a lamp with his cell flash light and club soda!! #impressed @username @username http://t.co/idAxXOgXBD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Thank you- God's ALWAYS loving us and WANTING to SAVE us from ourselves though-Never Too Late and never too Bad or Big for HIM		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username 2-0!  Undefeated so far as a Moc! Nice! #chattanoogastrong!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username -2-0... 3rd forfeited- We think he heard Clay & DJ saying John came to "Crack Skulls-NOT to play" & faked inj. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Great Day J took 4th at Hokie Open and Mocs had a good day! @username @username @username @username http://t.co/nDiQIPTTl4		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username  I Have known you for a while. Your face-yes, but  look in your eyes is not "busted up" - It is FIRED UP!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  let me know what she says!  Are you going to finish 10th grade 1st?  So exciting!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username Dear Live-Updater, YOU'RE KILLING ME, SMALLS!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username It looks like #Treatyoself day at Granma's!!!!  Adorable!!!!  So happy for you- and for her for having #1 Fun Granma EVER!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Big Day for @username in Eastern Michigan Duals! Beat Michigan State 24-13, Northern Illinois 34-9 and Kent State 20-15		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username @username @username  Pamela- I know you want Kyle in ORANGE running through the T next year!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username TRUE!  I will never wear a real diamond after seeing BLOOD DIAMONDS!  I talk to K about it-she pretends 2 be deaf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Eric Clapton - Tears in  heaven Unplugged (4/14): http://t.co/YcrA43zTCW via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I totally hate that!!!!!   (What is snapchat again??)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username - Can you talk to your friend and get this worked out??!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I just left HHS meeting-the speaker kicked it off with a trivia question-When was the last year burros were 12-0?...... NEVER!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Wait til you have KIDS! Their purpose in life is to convince you that you are not cool OR funny, but instead crazy & embarrassing.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[TN Natives Wrestling at the Scuffle This Year @username http://t.co/SLtLcbia03		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  #ChattanoogaStrong is ON A ROLL!  Keep it up, Mocs!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username Isn't it AWESOME when the parents come to visit!!!!?????? haha #sorrynotsorry  @username @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username -this is true, I'm pretty sure!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username You are a busy man, @username! HHS last night for round 3 playoff, Memphis next Fri. night. #HaveFun :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Way to go, @username!!!  You need to keep wearing your shorts backwards if you want to!!!!  #CHATTANOOGASTRONG		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username ANOTHER Moc having a #CHATTANOOGASTRONG Day!!!!  Congratulations!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username - sorry for painful loss - but Great Day, Shawn!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Great Job - - So HAPPY to have you in Chatt!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username WON Navy Classic today! #ChattanoogaStrong- Celebrate Big!!  Soon coaches will say "On to the next one" http://t.co/I8C99xCrF9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Held breath for 7 hrs, keeping up with Navy Classic match-by-match from 721 mi away-exhausted!  WON it- worth it!  #UTCWrestlingMomProblems		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Looking @username - just starting fight!!!! DO IT, DUSTIN!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Ortiz is Not intimidated by the biggest fight of his life" UFC announcer- duh!!  He is not intimidated by anyone! Going into 3rd!!  Go, D!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username "NO FEAR in THAT MAN!"  Damn Straight!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Fantastic 15 min with 2 of the finest flyweights in the nation!!".. Now wait for decision- you are awesome @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  decision 27-30- B. Giving Dustin huge props- entire post-fight interview @username class act-but ORTIZ will get him soon!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I have cursed ONCE on Twitter- during heat of @username battle- @username &@username "favorited"-thanks! http://t.co/w2fpVYl693		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I know you would rather have been in Annapolis today with your new team WINNING the Navy Classic! Soon!  Welcome to Chatt!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username If I had a nickel....!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username When I read this I could HEAR your voice and see your silly/sweet face!!!!!! http://t.co/OGfgq23OnQ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[That young man looks #ChattanoogaStrong to me.  We Love the MOCS! @username  @username @username @username http://t.co/s7qKKbLUpm		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[NFL player Benjamin Watson's Ferguson post viral - He expresses all "sides" - and then offers the REAL CURE! @username http://t.co/QC62fU5KB4		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username reminds me-you asking J-"Did you tell your momma you tried to break my neck? i just looked at coach like-WHAT!?"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username What can we do? People do not generally CHOOSE to be homeless, hungry and freezing to death as temps drop.  What can we do?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[We love our James and thank all of you who love him too!!  Obituary: James Carter Shrader http://t.co/TFOJbTXfwK via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username GET out THERE!!!!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Shoulders - For King & Country (2014): http://t.co/4lsrhSUeZa via @username from deb-pls take a moment with headphones and eyes closed!! ilu		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Right?! Such a wonderful young man- who knew thousands of people wanted him?  #VolForLife I won't miss a game! @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username SO EXCITED!!!!  1st time CJ wrote Her name AND his at same time!Genius @username @username @username http://t.co/ddSHWrUEB1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username You may be a dreamer-but you also seem to do a little work, believe in yourself & team and NEVER GIVE UP http://t.co/e0Ma3a6vVU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username - Aweome match!!!!!  Watching @username winning 2-0.... Missed second TD @username of mat by inches!!!  Go MOCS!!!!!!		]]></document>
</author>