<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="d4e76cdb-11e7-44ca-ad47-2fcf718f2fd8" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[Tiene sentido ... 'There Is A Huge Threat To Apple And Google That You've Never Heard Of' - Business Insider http://t.co/0cGUHNZn		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[¡Buena idea! - Facebook Is Clearly Planning On Trying To Destroy Google With Its Own Search Engine - Business Insider http://t.co/VfkQjAmc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hablando de patentes en USA ... Microsoft patent shows Holodeck-style, full-room “immersive display”, http://t.co/GKl6SVg0		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Semantic technologies for the publishing and media industries | @username http://t.co/bukVa01F #semantics		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Apple Might Bring Siri To Macs - Business Insider http://t.co/Uf0kopih		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[3 Ways Social Media Is Reshaping the Political Landscape http://t.co/4mStpQoz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Telefónica steps into augmented reality - http://t.co/aWibSlb4 - Telecoms http://t.co/ZK6hCQFX		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sobre TV y Redes sociales. 'Tuning In Social Media To Turn On What You’ll Like' - http://t.co/ZIc9Is27 http://t.co/CsduX8Yj		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Study urges CIOs to choose open source first - Software - Technology - News - http://t.co/zS8mQOp5 http://t.co/bfVdTiVk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Following the VC Money: http://t.co/Ey6zcuRb | http://t.co/mFjAKcqy http://t.co/ohSf8OQA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sobre el famoso índice H, 'Study Attempts To Predict Scientists' Career Success' - Slashdot http://t.co/6ZPAxbIB		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[5 things you need to know about cloud in Europe — Cloud Computing News http://t.co/SBsJ92AD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante! 'The Social Library: How Public Libraries Are Using Social Media' http://t.co/dtK7R99K		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[New Evidence That IPOs Are Bad For Growth - Business Insider http://t.co/MdWv7lXN		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Medicare Bills Rise As Records Turn Electronic - Slashdot http://t.co/lLj9A0OY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why aren’t universities creating engaging mobile platforms for students? — Tech News and Analysis http://t.co/0pftbvuw		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google no gana en Rusia ...Yandex Gives Google A One-Two Punch In Russia ... | TechCrunch http://t.co/hxcPw3GL		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[¡Interesante! ... Can you gamify content curation? This startup thinks so — Online Video News http://t.co/IrBixigM		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Internet-Media Employment Fuels Digital Job Growth | Media - Advertising Age http://t.co/LVTv40VI		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[El mercado de smartphones crecerá a buen ritmo. 'The State Of The Internet [SLIDE DECK]' - Business Insider http://t.co/gSOMaEGO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How Big Data Is Improving Healthcare http://t.co/kQLiCHBr		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Data Markets & the Data Economy - http://t.co/ZIc9Is27 http://t.co/0t2IDBhE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Semantic Targeting Increases Online Ad Reach Up to 73%, Improves Lift Performance Up to ¡Muy interesante! - 48% http://t.co/ax3G7hOs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[BBC Is Building a Music Streaming Service [REPORT] http://t.co/zowQr3Pt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[En busca de la monetización ... 'Twitter Partners With Nielsen on New Tool to Measure Brand Impact' http://t.co/R8r6oxU0		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Más sobre monetizar redes sociales ... 'Turning social media into cash: 6 insights from the new tech titans' http://t.co/EsTc6rX0		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[AOL looking to spin out Techcrunch’s CrunchBase — Tech News and Analysis http://t.co/79gPlnDF		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Después de las gafas ... ¿también relojes? - 'New patent hints at Google Glass wristwatch | Crave' - CNET http://t.co/cLiVkrHz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[On What Shores Will Semantic Tech Be Better Commercialized? - http://t.co/ZIc9Is27 http://t.co/oTgZqADE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante. 'Google-Publisher Deal Ignores Elephant In The Room: Fair Use' http://t.co/nyOHpK0P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Autopublicación en formato electrónico sin pasar por Amazon. 'Ganxy offers an easier way to sell and market ebooks', http://t.co/Z2RX0J41		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Vaya, españoles en la nube, 'Spanish startup Besol wants a slice of the cloud-broker pie' http://t.co/m3PJE3Rg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Las APIs, entre Amazon y Salesforce. 'Business process API-ification: The LEGO promise fulfilled' http://t.co/iAyrcoDM		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Curiosidades ... 'The typical Twitter user is a young woman with an iPhone and 208 followers' — Tech News and Analysis http://t.co/nbeoU0Fd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hoy la cosa va de presencia femenina ... From Twitter to Dropbox, how many female executives do top startups have?, http://t.co/XbhZpXsh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante. Con datos de Gartner, 'A Fertile Field For Semantic Tech: Social CRM', http://t.co/CsxwHzqI		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No es malo que te rechacen un paper ;-) - 'Rejected Papers Get More Citations When Eventually Published' - Slashdot http://t.co/32pg5NMt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[¿Cuándo publicar tus posts (o enviar tus mails o tuitear)?- 'What's The Best Time Of Day To Send Emails?' [Infographic] http://t.co/Rcnb449Q		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HTML5 vs. Apps: Why The Debate Matters, And Who Will Win - Business Insider http://t.co/dqoXAIWg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante. Resumido en el 3er párrafo desde el final,'It's Not About You: The Truth About Social Media Marketing', http://t.co/ldPb3dM3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Structured Data First Steps: Adding Schema Location Markup to Your Website - Search Engine Watch (#SEW) http://t.co/NZxcg0mH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[BII MOBILE INSIGHTS: Why Mobile Search Matters - Business Insider http://t.co/pt0o3zOX		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante, ¿Flash ha muerto? 'ReadWriteWeb DeathWatch: Flash' http://t.co/QnGaAABr		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Parece que rNews (antes IPTC) quiere acercarse a http://t.co/bdxq46CV, 'Catching Up With rNews At NYC SemTech', http://t.co/8SDJAAIt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Big Data To Drive $232 Billion In IT Spending Through 2016 | TechCrunch http://t.co/RlYgWPKn		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[5 Ways Semantic Technologies Help Us All - http://t.co/ZIc9Is27 http://t.co/RYdpD5pt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pfizer Moves Semantic Tech Forward, Helping Business Respond To Cost Pressures And Realize Efficiency Gains, http://t.co/PhXVbK7R		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Competencia para Klout. 'Beyond Klout: Better Ways To Measure Social Media Influence' http://t.co/Xf2C1OFd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google siempre por delante. 'Google Video Promotes Gay Marriage - What About Other Tech Giants?' http://t.co/NVKG9RbH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante, sobre derechos de autor y Twiter.' New Twitter policy lets users see tweets pulled down for copyright' http://t.co/9wKuG9k9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google redesigns search to make space for more info, kick the sidebar to the curb -- Engadget http://t.co/JnxBRrT3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Sergei Brin, founder of Google, when asked for best advice says: "Be brief in your emails" @username #GVsummit		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Best Semantic Web Blogs List | @username @username http://t.co/sP6iTz8o #semantics		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hadoop ya no es suficiente. 'Facebook's New Big Data Tool Cranks Up Hadoop - And It's Open Source' http://t.co/uAG14efJ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Un poco exagerado, ¿no? 'How A Simple Gmail Search Could Lead To An Invasion Of Your Privacy' http://t.co/zd25liCR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[¿Será esto verdad? '42% of Windows Users Plan To Switch To Apple' - Business Insider http://t.co/UzCyWnp2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Muy interesante. 'Facebook Has A Business Model Problem' http://t.co/2YL6nBkD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: UI Guidelines for mobile and tablet web app design http://t.co/zbFy3O5S @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[jajaja, 'Oprah Is Tweeting Her Love For Microsoft's Surface From Her iPad' - Business Insider http://t.co/uwrdvgsT		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante caso de uso de IBM, 'Key Benefits of Using Semantic Web Technology' - http://t.co/ZIc9Is27 http://t.co/iHMfWN59		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Coping with the Future of Big Data - http://t.co/ZIc9Is27 http://t.co/13iZLmad		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Corpus of tweets in Spanish annotated for sentiment analysys now freely available   http://t.co/BKYLGf9Z		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: GeorgiaTech Team Wins $2.7 Million Award to Advance Big-Data Technology for DARPA | @username http://t.co/jzBtwboV		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Marc Andreessen: Not every startup should be a Lean Startup or embrace the pivot — Tech News and Analysis http://t.co/sly1qADz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Corpus of tweets in Spanish annotated for sentiment analysys now freely available   http://t.co/BKYLGf9Z		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Daedalus Releases New Version of Multilingual Semantic Proofreading Tool - http://t.co/ZIc9Is27 http://t.co/AbTIYudA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[¿Google también hace relojes?... Google Smart Watch Design - Business Insider http://t.co/TncHfgpE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante. "Zappos CEO Tony Hsieh: Tips For Success" - Business Insider http://t.co/XvwdT7qe		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[BSkyB ofrecerá anuncios personalizados en TV. "A TV that knows who you are" - http://t.co/aWibSlb4 http://t.co/jrzql7fr		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Competitive Challenge. Extraction of Drug-Drug Interactions from BioMedical Texts http://t.co/YA3u5kUO | @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pay-by-tweet service launched on Twitter - http://t.co/aWibSlb4 http://t.co/n4moyR2f		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Será interesante ver si esto se confirma. 'Facebook May Already Be Taking Away Searches From Google' http://t.co/gEmjV4DZ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[¿También Intel en en la guerra de la TV por streaming? - 'Intel TV service already being tested by hundreds of users' http://t.co/uExzV8A1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[¿Confías en tus ads?. 'ComScore Says 5.3 Trillion Ads Shown In 2012, But 3 In 10 Are Never Seen' | TechCrunch http://t.co/3BNUNtmj		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Habrá que pensar en cómo monetizar ¿no? 'Skype calls now equivalent to one-third of global phone traffic' |Ars Technica http://t.co/CThqzRJP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante, no siempre más clientes es mejor. 'Why Fewer Customers Will Help You Grow Faster' | Inc. 5000 http://t.co/XA5wDqLs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Una API de Twitter para anuncions. 'Twitter tries new tool to unlock ads' - http://t.co/ZjaoxvMmn8 http://t.co/oxHREqOQfS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Daedalus, mentioned in Gartner " Who's Who in Text Analytics" report  http://t.co/EYPF6piHA1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Daedalus Releases New Version of Sentimentalytics - http://t.co/QCZ6i0H3rB http://t.co/hjSc5S88D4		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The Teen Who Got $30 Million From Yahoo Did Not Build His Startup's App (Or Invent Its Technology) - Business Insider http://t.co/CDw0o3AOEX		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante. 'Microsoft Skewers Google For Giving Your Personal Data To App Developers' - Business Insider http://t.co/CPJupF9DCV		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Daedalus Releases New Version of Sentimentalytics - http://t.co/QCZ6i0H3rB http://t.co/t5rauBrqKl		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Daedalus Releases New Version of Sentimentalytics - http://t.co/QCZ6i0H3rB http://t.co/3o19SGOa6H		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[New version of Sentimentalytics: our plug-in for the semantic analysis of social media | El Blog de Daedalus http://t.co/AU2AcrKsXt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The internet of things gets industrial strength collaboration with GE, Electric Imp & Quirky — Tech News and Analysis http://t.co/GSe8MfVGGW		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fujitsu Develops Technology That Turns Paper Into a Touchscreen http://t.co/e8StSTclVz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why The Traditional Sales Model Can't Sell Enterprise Software – ReadWrite http://t.co/ZBMQlTQSoO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[With Pulse, LinkedIn Is Becoming The Newspaper Of The Future – ReadWrite http://t.co/IABWTsDabt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[¿Adobe está olvidando Flash? - Flash Takes Another Step Towards Death As Unity Drops Support | TechCrunch http://t.co/RIgSKs39we		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante, "The ex-MySQL gang is back together, pushing MariaDB as a neutral ‘bridge’" — Tech News and Analysis http://t.co/uMLFOPoYaV		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Adiós a los reproductores de DVD, 'Amazon reportedly introducing set-top box this fall' http://t.co/MGv6hgD96N		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[¿Google imitando a Yahoo con Summ.ly? Yo creo que no ... 'Google Buys Wavii for $30 Million http://t.co/NuQIu1Kf3o		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[8 Risks When You Ignore Social Media | http://t.co/YnmAC4JUKO http://t.co/IHnOnaFlvT		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante, 'How Software Developers Really Spend Their Time' – ReadWrite http://t.co/2bI2IPhqxv		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[New version of Sentimentalytics: our plug-in for the semantic analysis of social media | El Blog de Daedalus http://t.co/SYTHOre4es		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[De la búsqueda al filtrado de información. 'How The Internet Of Things Will Revolutionize Search' – ReadWrite http://t.co/4SwtSwcnhx		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hombre, decir que Yahoo o Facebook no trabajan con 'big data' ... The reality of big data - Business Insider http://t.co/y9yKgSb5gC		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pero si acaba de llegar el 4G ... Samsung ready for 5G rollout in 2020, has reportedly pulled down 1Gbps in tests http://t.co/VsOt5cT3qn		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google Plus Is A Desolated Wasteland - Business Insider http://t.co/TqvOTdyJ5C		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Interesante ... 'Visualization is the future: 6 startups re-imagining how we consume data' — Tech News and Analysis http://t.co/b9envFvrd8		]]></document>
</author>