<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="ed4bf592-b7e0-4b74-ac13-441aa8dbbc95" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: WHEN YOU TELL GRANDPA 60'S MUSIC WAS TRASH #KnockOutVines http://t.co/IVv6O3BrOr"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I've been hurt so bad but I still love so hard. I admire my heart for that.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Girls these days.. http://t.co/5cte0m6cqo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Yellow motherfucking claw ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Snow white successfully led on 7 short guys and ended up choosing the dude that was 6'4 if that ain't relevant to real life then idk what is		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: Bach to back FIFA avond met @username http://t.co/41ctUjOUc1"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bobby Shmurda is facing up to 25 years in prison for second degree murder yet Iggy Azalea is still free after killing music ..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username "will hump later"  ????????????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I love how liqour turns flat chests into mountains.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[???????????????????????????? "@username: when she slips a finger in your asshole http://t.co/VCnmwVxESv"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[She is still on my mind and sleep is hard to find. Everything reminds me that she's not beside me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I do think of her and the ways that things were, when she was still there to guide me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username dont forget angry people.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This could be us but you keep playing.  http://t.co/YXYI9sfOUI		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm going crazy, but I will always use my best sence.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Made it through a hurricane, so I'm celebrating with a Mary Jane.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I will unintionally offend you eventually, because you can't comprehend a different opinion.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's funny how dumb people have smart phones.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This is what I wanna make, I don't care if it sells.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username lol also cold as fuck, difficult langauge and next to Russia.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: When you're pre-gaming with your bros and the taxi shows up http://t.co/ABr6XKv2Ho"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I should get you baseball gloves for christmas, so you can catch feelings.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT ????????????????"@username: When your girl says "you aint getting none tonight"... but you already cheated http://t.co/76BGtzoLCr"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Rare film maar wel super tof.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username that looks.like my local mc donalds.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm signing off with a crotch grab.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[GELD SLAAPT NOOIT, DAAROM BEN IK SNACHTS ALTIJD WAKKER.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pfff, said yes didnt get it tho. No xmas present for me. http://t.co/kGt6IwA9zv		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My hero http://t.co/1gm0roi5sK		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Parents ???? "@username: Damn that's real http://t.co/Sa15bjZr3I"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username yeah lets eat a wasp, it's entire family will chase you, trying to kill you.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[He's too strong to get to close to anyone, because everyone who promised they would stay, turned their backs and walked away.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username WHERE CAN I PURCHASE THE SHOES FROM THE PICTURE? I LUV EM!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[SUV swerving like it's O.J.'s car.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's so late that it's early.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I will give some a second chance for 2015.

Mistakes are forgotten, no footprints of any miss steps.  

????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username everybody hates greg		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username if you insist lolol nty		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nudes is a 5 letter word

Send is a 4 letter word

5 minus 4 equals 1

Just 1 nude can make anyone's day 

Simple algebra.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username the wife probably cheats because the nice husband is considered "boring"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thanks for the compliment		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thats how I look when a bitch gives me a bad blowjob		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: We've all lost a good bro to a girl... R.I.P Old Best Friend"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Someone with shit to hide is someone who I kick aside.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Stunt like a bitch.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The adrinaline rush of creating what you think about... with who thinks about you.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username yeah that would be fucking intents.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thats not much I can drink that easely in a day with coca cola		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When you in bed watching Netflix all night and you keep getting disturbt... http://t.co/3oFHR9NCEJ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Okay, I defo found my new tv show to watch. Sons of anarchy. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Seen all them kewl shows on netflix already glad i found another one.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When a girl tells me I'm a good kisser but she still won't let me hit yet. http://t.co/60iUTEfJO3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[NEW YEARS EVE GOT ME LIKE http://t.co/vqVh4gKSPS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[JE KAN ME VERLATEN IN 2015 IDGAF, M'N VADER STARTE DIE TREND IN 2007.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[All I wear last king's gear man that shit so ill.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Iz u down is my teamsong take your thong of put me on.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than everyone knowing is that no one knows..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[We the cause of all the comotion.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Voices in my head? I need choices in my bed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Gekkigheid "@username: The haunted forest http://t.co/xUVJiKoF44"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Girl you fucking with the best, take a picture while I'm deep up in it. And if they living right next, I bet they know my name in a minute.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username i know bro ???????? BMS the best.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When you hand me the AUX-cord.
https://t.co/p58rHpHeor		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[At the snackbar being order 69, bitch knowns whats up.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm still drunk to you		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No matter what we breed, we are still made of greed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Every high school and college girl ever https://t.co/G38puTicIZ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When momma says I need to stop playing those videogames.  https://t.co/5Bpn9AtABH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When people say really mean things to you.. http://t.co/r2iKOxIIde		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: my "won't speak until i'm spoken to" game is strong af."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You know what fame is? Sitting with the woman of your dreams and forgetting what her name is.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username where did it end		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username why the fuck he chilling with headphones		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[FIFA THINGS "@username: When your strike partner shoots instead of laying it off to you for an open goal.. http://t.co/wWVCEYQ7ga"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[She rides me when the lights go off she climbes on top, her body rocking we don't stop.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[She ride me like a pro, she did this before.. I hold her tight no letting go till she says she cant take no more.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Im speechless. All I say is oooh oooh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username tell that the muslims lol		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[What’s the difference between a knife and a female arguing?

A knife has a point.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username lol how you get all those hoes		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A long time I've been alone. For years in a house but it wasn't a home. I've made brothers of a different kind instead.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I will not be commanded.

I will not be controlled.

And I will not let my future go on without the help of my soul.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username the woman from the pic can be my baby momma aswell		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username also a beautiful face I'd like to nut all over		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wingman 2.0 right here		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You were not feeling me, cause I was not feeling 'we'.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ya'll just some major haters and some math minors.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[WHEN THE ALCOHOL KICKS IN http://t.co/K3LN13CK9l.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Baby you're fired, your girlfriend hired.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username what????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: shoutout to the friends that still like me

all two of you"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username lol i knew this day would come.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username what a thot		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[K RINO - Grand deception ????????????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Barber : what do u want?

Client : you know that moment when you pour your milk into your tea?

Barber : say no more http://t.co/ylapJmaXwN		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[GET ME SOME SLOOTS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Flaws ain't flaws when it's you that make the calls!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ty Dolla $ign ft. Wiz Khalifa & DJ Mustard - or nah remix ????????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I can only imagine how it feels like..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Kanye during the day
Drake at night		]]></document>
</author>