<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="f3af2ca2-dbfb-4447-a4f2-dfdfdda58640" lang="en">
	<document><![CDATA[@username what about Robin Ruiter?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Thumbing through bill after bill.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username then you say: Claudio, BRAVO!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HET IS NIET TE GELOVEN		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[JE MOEDER IS JE MOEDER NIET, JE VADER IS JE VADER NIET, CUMMINS, HOERENJONG		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[???????????? Listen carefully to how a person speaks about other people to you. This is how they will speak about you to other people.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I would like a welcome to the world of fast money, fast cars, big diamond rings, big chains and girls of fake smiles and broken hearts.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm not looking for my real love, I won't find it here.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Choices are sacrifices, giving something up that you want for something that you want more.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Promise this to you: I will get us out the hood.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If she keep blowing I might explode, never seen a girl like her  before		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Misgunners everywhere.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Substitution, add me in.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I calculate a home invation. Devide yours legs and count to three.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Welcome to hell's paradise.. I always knew life was a pair of dice.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If you leave this time I feel you'll be gone for good...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Everyday I wake up celebrate and shit, why? Cause I dodged the bullet from a crazy bitch.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username lol she is Elizabeth in White Collars!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sorry Sierra Leone, one day we'll right the wrongs.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Free your mind, let your consious be free.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: Is it because I'm black?"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I SWEAR TO GOD IM MOVING ON TUTUUTUUU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Chris Brown - X ????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username lol its San Marino, beat the 11-0 from the Dutch.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Foreplay? That's child's play. Making love is my forte. Shots at you cause I'm thirsty. Damn right ima eat that pussy.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[August Alsina - Testify ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's bad ya'll, lost some homies on the way, it's sad ya'll.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Jason Derulo - Stupid Love ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Highclass but just surrounded by these low lifes .		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You need that late night, we can both make love to the daylight, you know I can't stay, right?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: I LOVE MAKING PEOPLE WHO HATE ME ALREADY HATE ME EVEN MORE????"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[ON SOME SERIOUS SHIT... IF YOU IN YA 20'S AND GRADUATED.. FUCK ARE U STILL DOING TRYING TO GET BITCHES IN HIGHSCHOOL..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ima blame you for what they say about me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I can see from this high up, you ain't got a heart girl.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username misread it - deleted it, so it never excisted.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Want to but I can't help it, I love the way it feels. It got me stuck between my fantasy and what is real. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When you're the first one who has to go home after a chill day with the squad http://t.co/IAnzMhGwKQ.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I M IN THE BAY WITH HER, BUT I'LL SEND HER BACK HOME SO YOU CAN LAY WITH HER.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HAHAHAHA "@username: This from @username is both brilliant and disturbing. http://t.co/VqPG6sU9XO"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username few more goals and you're out to 3rd place.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Girl you know, I'm here to save you. Me and them boys, we ain't the same boo. I won't love it and leave it..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I won't treat you like I treat them, you're the cremé de la cremé.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I used to class in the day and run away in the night, now I'm ruler of the upperclass and I don't even try.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username arthur pikk hqhaha pik is Dutch for penis.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nobody saw the struggle, they just see the reward. They focus on the peace but they never saw the war.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fucked up
Insecure
Neurotic
Emotional

So if someone tells you they're *fine*... think again.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nelson Freitas - Something Good. ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Red roses, white wine, the candles are lit today. It's all for you. Hoping underneath that nice dress is some lingerie.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The rt koning right here.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Wanna build myself a future abroad, in whatever country, doing whatever that makes me happy. As long as i'm gone.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nothing else to do but to get some clothes and pack. About to runaway and never looking back.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: Sometimes distance reveals to you who's worth keeping and who's worth letting go."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: RAISE YOUR HAND IF YOU HATE THOSE PEOPLE THAT ONLY HIT U UP WHEN THEY NEED SHIT????"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Deep. "@username: The truth hurts but it doesn't kill. Lies may please, but they don't heal."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Somebody's girl is on my body, naked & shaking.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tryna forgive you for abandoning me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My heart is growing cold, gotta sleep with warmer covers.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HAHAHAHAHA "@username: WHEN YOU FIND THE WHITE KID THAT CALLED YOU A NIGGER ON CALL OF DUTY http://t.co/QiDwS6P59d"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[????????????????????"@username: GIRL: LETS JUST CHILL & WATCH NETFLIX

ME: http://t.co/ghMY3AKB8Q"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[TERING WAT BEN IK STIJF EN HET IS NIET EENS ME LUL..:(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I DO, DO YOU? "@username: We all have that one friend http://t.co/hqi42ctZKo"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Started out as friends, then became lovers. When we knew in the end, that was not the plan.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[WAT EEN GOAL VAN ME NEEF CRISTIANO RONALDO!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: That Ronaldo got me like... http://t.co/forPaiCFHx"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[LIVERPOOL WORDT AFGEDROOGD, GA MAAR NAAR HUIS LIVERPOOL.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Will I ever meet my wife? Maybe one day? Have a few kids? Gonna travel out the stae?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: This is great ???? https://t.co/xWw3rVOgf2"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[PLEURIS FIFA STA JE 3-1 ACHTER RAAK JE 4X DE PAAL VERVOLGENS UIT EEN COUNTER DE 4-1 ????????????????????????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I love her till my last breaths gone.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pussy bomb, tik-tok. Eyes locked, lip lock, thing popped, I'm done. No love, heart sprung, baby gimme some yum yum.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Fuck a blogdawg, cause one day we gone meet. Ima spaz on your ass like I'm on E.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[There's nothing worst than feeling like a ghost.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm terrified.. like I've seen an UFO. Everything ain't what I used to know.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[ALL YOU HATERS SO PLAYED OUT, YA'LL SO 1999, AND I'M LIKE SO THESE AIN'T EVEN OUT YET, YOU CAN'T FIND IT ONLINE.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why would I trip up for the bullshit?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm lost, I need a sign. Lead the way, I'll be okay.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT "@username: Wow
       So weekend
          Very sleep
   Much relax
       Such break"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[HALAAA MADRID, DAT WERD TIJD.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hahahahaha "@username: This could be us but you "too pretty" to suck dick. http://t.co/AH9x0GlA08"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: When Nas said http://t.co/bv5QERhklO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: When she finally let's you fuck and the dick game stronger than she expected http://t.co/YYXQIcip26		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: Lmao this dude http://t.co/uyO1ZP4f8E		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pretty eyes and that smile girl i'm a fool for that.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I don't want nobody but me talking to you until you fall asleep.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'll live all my life around the thought of me and you.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[August Alsina ft. Nicki Minaj - No Love (remix).		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[August Alsina - Kissing On My Tattoos		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[GO BACK AND FORTH IN , MORE BEEF THAT YOU CAN PACK A FORK IN		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm a good boy, I just do bad things.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username when a thot finally sucks your dick but she "sucks" at it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dreaming about the things we could be.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I found light at the end of the tunnel. That's why I keep my head high.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When I try to play sports..

https://t.co/rHgXOgzhwG		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[On a scheme for the green, if you know what I mean.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Put your bottles in the air, let me hear the ching-ching.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Life a rockstar lifestyle just like Sting, chick is a rockstar just like Pink.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username this is real fucked up, and 99% of the time I laugh about any offensive joke.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username i wont cause it didnt offend me personally, just in general offensive towards others. Wont unfollow for one stupid ass tweet		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Chris Brown - 2012 to turn your mood.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[When you need that late night.. we can both make love till the daylight..		]]></document>
</author>